<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://daorren.github.io/osmofeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-10-23T02:29:40.499Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://daorren.github.io/osmofeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://daorren.github.io/osmofeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend Reading — 👋 Any desk is a standing desk if you’re short enough]]></title>
        <id>634b4a70725d383ca43f088e</id>
        <link href="https://labnotes.org/weekend-reading-any-desk-is-a-standing-desk-if-youre-short-enough/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T23:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we help a machine generate art, so we can out-source our thought leadership, wash in WFG, and set up our OpenTable profile.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Assaf Arkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Upload Files to Azure using NestJS and typeORM with MySQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/upload-files-to-azure-using-nestjs-and-typeorm-with-mysql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/upload-files-to-azure-using-nestjs-and-typeorm-with-mysql/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T23:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images and videos are examples of huge files that might be stored in your database. And this might impact the performance of your applications because of the amount of space that those files can take up.  Also, it expands the database, which makes backups larger and slower. Because of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Destiny Erhabor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Layouts – How to Use CSS Grid and Flex to Create a Responsive Web Page]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-layouts-use-css-grid-and-flex-to-create-responsive-webpages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-layouts-use-css-grid-and-flex-to-create-responsive-webpages/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T23:12:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your web layout is to your website what a floor plan is to a building. Without them, you’re just building castles in the air.  The first thing to do when you have a website or application to build or design is to decide on the layout. This is important]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ophy Boamah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A centered CSS grid with full-width components (#snippet)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/snippets/a-centered-css-grid-with-full-width-components/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/snippets/a-centered-css-grid-with-full-width-components/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not too long ago, I was looking into refactoring my site to go all in with CSS grid!
I've been aiming for a classical centered blog layout with flexible side margins. The content should be 65 characters wide at max. But (!) I wanted to be able to break free, and some components should go full-width by setting a class. And it should all work with CSS grid.
After fiddling with it for a while, I didn't reach a satisfying result and decided to do it another day. In the meantime, Ryan Mulligan's post "Layout Breakouts with CSS Grid" provided the CSS solution I was looking for (see it in action on CodePen).
The solution: named grid-template-columns and some math

Put all your content in a content wrapper element that defines named grid areas:
.content {
  --gap: clamp(1rem, 6vw, 3rem);
  --full: minmax(var(--gap), 1fr);
  --content: min(50ch, 100% - var(--gap) * 2);
  --popout: minmax(0, 2rem);
  --feature: minmax(0, 5rem);

  display: grid;
  grid-template-columns:
    [full-start] var(--full)
    [feature-start] var(--feature)
    [popout-start] var(--popout)
    [content-start] var(--content) [content-end]
    var(--popout) [popout-end]
    var(--feature) [feature-end]
    var(--full) [full-end];
}

And then control all the component widths using grid template areas. 💯
.content > * {
  grid-column: content;
}
.popout {
  grid-column: popout;
}
.feature {
  grid-column: feature;
}
.full {
  grid-column: full;
}

The post even includes a beautiful visualization that explains what's going on. 👏
I love it. 💙 Thank you, Ryan!


          
          
            Reply to Stefan]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is an ORM – The Meaning of Object Relational Mapping Database Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-an-orm-the-meaning-of-object-relational-mapping-database-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-an-orm-the-meaning-of-object-relational-mapping-database-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T18:18:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Object Relational Mapping (ORM) is a technique used in creating a "bridge" between object-oriented programs and, in most cases, relational databases [/news/what-is-a-relational-database-rdbms-definition/]. Put another way, you can see the ORM as the layer that connects object oriented programming [/news/four-pillars-of-object-oriented-programming/] (OOP) to relational databases.  When interacting with a database using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Ethernet Protocol Works – A Complete Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-complete-guide-to-the-ethernet-protocol/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-complete-guide-to-the-ethernet-protocol/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T17:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you’ve been aware of it or not, you’ve probably used the Ethernet in the past. Does this cable look familiar? (Source: Wikipedia [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ethernet_physical_layer#/media/File:EthernetCableYellow3.jpg] )Ethernet is extremely popular, and is the most widely used Data Link Layer protocol, at least where the devices are linked by physical cables (rather than]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wiping the map clean]]></title>
        <id>https://golangweekly.com/issues/433</id>
        <link href="https://golangweekly.com/issues/433"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#​433 — October 21, 2022


Unsubscribe  |  Read on the Web



    
Together with 
        
          
          
          
        
      

    
    

The Go Weekly Newsletter




  





  
  
The Go WebAssembly ABI at a Low Level — Go 1.11 added initial support for compiling Go to WebAssembly (something TinyGo also supports) but how does the interaction between WASM-compiled Go and the broader (often JavaScript-based) environment work? A very extensive (and entertaining) writeup of a conference talk given at GoLab 2022 earlier this month.
Xe Iaso 


  
  
Proposal: A Simple Way to Clear a Map — We’re getting a good run of proposals recently, and Russ Cox is back with a way to more simply clear a map – simply delete(m) – simple enough, you might think, but potential problems have already…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Golang Weekly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Object Oriented Programming in Python – Full Crash Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crash-course-object-oriented-programming-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crash-course-object-oriented-programming-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T22:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Object Oriented programming, or "OOP" for short, is a way of writing code that relies on the concepts of classes and objects.  The main benefit of writing your code in an object-oriented way is to structure your program into simple, reusable pieces of code. Stick with me through this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Wagner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CRUD Operations – Crud Definition in Programming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crud-operations-crud-definition-in-programming/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crud-operations-crud-definition-in-programming/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T21:54:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When interacting with a database or working with an API, you'll often encounter the term CRUD. It is a popular acronym for the four basic operations or functions that a model (in the case of an API) or a database management system uses. This is an acronym everyone learning computer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computer Programmer Salary – How Much Do Coders Make?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/computer-programmer-salary-how-much-do-coders-make/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/computer-programmer-salary-how-much-do-coders-make/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T19:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coding is one of the most popular and in-demand careers. There are many reasons why people choose a career in coding and computer science. The technology field offers promising and diverse job prospects in several industries, job security, a generally comfortable starting salary, and increased high-earning potential as developers gain]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tableau VS Power BI – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tableau-vs-power-bi-whats-the-difference/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tableau-vs-power-bi-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T17:48:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tableau and Power BI are both data visualization and business intelligence tools. You can extract data with both tools, visualize the data, analyze it, and turn it into a piece of actionable information. In this article, you will learn what both Power BI and Tableau are in detail. I will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experiments Spell Doom for Decades-Old Explanation of Quantum Weirdness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=119930</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/physics-experiments-spell-doom-for-quantum-collapse-theory-20221020/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T14:20:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Physical-collapse theories have long offered a natural solution to the central mystery of the quantum world. But a series of increasingly precise experiments are making them untenable.              
The post Experiments Spell Doom for Decades-Old Explanation of Quantum Weirdness first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philip Ball</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code Google Docs with Flutter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-google-docs-with-flutter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-google-docs-with-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T14:15:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a Google Docs clone will help you learn a lot of new concepts. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Flutter to create a Google Docs clone. Rivaan Ranawat created this course. Rivaan has created many popular technical]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Reverting to Previous Commit – How to Revert to Last Commit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-reverting-to-previous-commit-how-to-revert-to-last-commit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-reverting-to-previous-commit-how-to-revert-to-last-commit/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T22:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git [/news/git-and-github-for-beginners/] is a great tool for version control. It also makes collaborating with others more efficient. In this article, you'll learn how to revert to previous commits when tracking your project with Git. The two commands we'll discuss in this article are git reset and git revert. These commands]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the Proton, the ‘Most Complicated Thing You Could Possibly Imagine’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=119773</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/inside-the-proton-the-most-complicated-thing-imaginable-20221019/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T14:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The positively charged particle at the heart of the atom is an object of unspeakable complexity, one that changes its appearance depending on how it is probed. We’ve attempted to connect the proton’s many faces to form the most complete picture yet.              
The post Inside the Proton, the ‘Most Complicated Thing You Could Possibly Imagine’ first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Charlie Wood and Merrill Sherman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard CS50 – Free Computer Science University Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/harvard-cs50/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/harvard-cs50/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T14:07:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard University's CS50 is one of the most popular beginner computer science courses in the world.  We just released the entire CS50 course–all 25 hours–on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. David J. Malan is widely considered to be one of the best computer science instructors. He teaches this course. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Command Line Tutorial – How to Use Common Terminal Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linux-command-line-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linux-command-line-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T23:33:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An operating system is a set of software layers between you and your computer's hardware.  The operating system (or OS) is a piece of software that controls all other application programs and helps you manage the hardware and software of your computer. Examples of popular operating systems are Windows,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Destiny Erhabor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wi-Fi Hacking 101 – How to Hack WPA2 and Defend Against These Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/wi-fi-hacking-101/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/wi-fi-hacking-101/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T20:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the world of Wi-Fi hacking, everybody. 💻. In my previous article [/news/linux-basics/], we talked about some basic Linux skills and tricks. In this article you are going to learn a basic Wi-Fi hacking procedure using those skills. You'll learn things such as how to:  1. Monitor Wi-Fi]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Iwugo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Append a String in Python – STR Appending]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/append-a-string-in-python-str-appending/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/append-a-string-in-python-str-appending/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T19:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll learn the different methods of appending strings in Python.  Another term commonly used when talking about appending strings is concatenation. So you'll often see these terms — append and concatenate — used interchangeably.  Either way, to append or concatenate strings means to add or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Go Handbook – Learn Golang for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/go-beginners-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/go-beginners-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T18:35:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Golang is an awesome, simple, modern, and fast programming language. It’s compiled, open source, and strongly typed. Golang – also called Go – was created by Google engineers with these main goals:  * make their projects compile (and run) faster  * be simple so people can pick it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flavio Copes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Cross-Platform Application with Next.js and Tauri]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-cross-platform-app-with-next-and-tauri/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-cross-platform-app-with-next-and-tauri/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T16:38:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tauri is a new Rust-based framework that builds an x86_64 cross-platform application for Windows, macOS, and Linux.  In this tutorial, we'll use Tauri and Next.js to build a desktop-based cross-platform application and publish it to the Snap store and AppImage. So why is building a cross-platform app, that works]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Computer Scientist Who’s Boosting Privacy on the Internet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=119841</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/the-computer-scientist-who-boosts-privacy-with-entropy-20221018/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T15:16:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harry Halpin wants our internet conversations to be more private. He’s helped create a new kind of network that might make it possible.             
The post The Computer Scientist Who’s Boosting Privacy on the Internet first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Nadis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Search Tips – How to Search Issues, Repos, and More Effectively on GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/github-search-tips/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/github-search-tips/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T19:27:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I was a beginner to open-source contributions, one of my greatest challenge was finding the correct projects/issues to work on. For the longest time I relied on resources curated by different writers on the internet (which were good, by the way). But I always wanted to find a way]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hillary Nyakundi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Explode – How to Split a String into an Array]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/php-explode-how-to-split-a-string-into-an-array/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/php-explode-how-to-split-a-string-into-an-array/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T17:19:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The PHP explode() function converts a string to an array. Each of the characters in the string is given an index that starts from 0. Like the built-in imlode()  function, the explode function does not modify the data (string). Syntax of the explode() Function The explode() function takes in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Show Upcoming Meetings for a Microsoft 365 User]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-show-upcoming-meetings-for-a-microsoft-365-user/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-show-upcoming-meetings-for-a-microsoft-365-user/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T17:08:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a web developer and you work with an organization that uses Microsoft 365, you probably use it to manage your meetings. In this tutorial, you'll learn how you can build a simple personal assistant in under 10 minutes that'll show a Microsoft 365 user the meetings they have]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Waldek Mastykarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Architect a Blockchain on Kubernetes – K8S Microservice Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-architect-a-blockchain-on-kubernetes-k8s-microservice-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-architect-a-blockchain-on-kubernetes-k8s-microservice-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T16:02:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will describe how to use microservices architecture and Kubernetes to build a blockchain.  The technologies usually used for blockchains are purpose-driven, and you can use them for other projects as well. The examples in this article can readily handle heavy loads and remain responsive and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kayode Adeniyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Lowercase a String in JavaScript – toLowerCase() in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-lowercase-a-string-in-javascript-tolowercase-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-lowercase-a-string-in-javascript-tolowercase-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T15:51:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strings are a fundamental part of working with JavaScript. And the toLowerCase()  method is one of the many integrated methods that you can use to work with strings. In this article, we'll see how to make strings lowercase with the toLowerCase()  method in Python. What is a String?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilenia Magoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Svelte in 23 Hours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-svelte-complete-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-svelte-complete-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T15:14:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Svelte is a front-end JavaScript framework for making interactive webpages. Svelte has grown in popularity quite a bit over the last few years. We just published a free 23-hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Svelte. Li Hau Tan developed this course. Li]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Interpret Black Box Models using LIME (Local Interpretable Model-Agnostic Explanations)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/interpret-black-box-model-using-lime/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/interpret-black-box-model-using-lime/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T15:12:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning models are black box models. By giving input to these models, we can get output based on the particular model we're using.  The way humans interpret things is different from how machines interpret them. So it's helpful to use tools that can turn the output from certain]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josua Antonius Naiborhu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mathematicians Discover the Fibonacci Numbers Hiding in Strange Spaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=119791</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/mathematicians-surprised-by-hidden-fibonacci-numbers-20221017/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T13:44:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent explorations of unique geometric worlds reveal perplexing patterns, including the Fibonacci sequence and the golden ratio.            
The post Mathematicians Discover the Fibonacci Numbers Hiding in Strange Spaces first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leila Sloman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Python? How the Interpreter Works and How to Write "Hello World" in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-python-beginners-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-python-beginners-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T13:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I am going to explain what Python is and how the Python interpreter works. Then you'll write your first "Hello World" program. What is Python? Python is a high-level programming language designed to do many tasks. It's based on the CPython interpreter which translates the Python code]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Five Layers Model? The Framework of the Internet Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-five-layers-model-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-five-layers-model-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T13:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computer Networks are a beautiful, amazing topic. Networks involve so much knowledge from different fields, from physics to algorithms.  When dealing with Computer Networks, there is one framework that puts everything into place – and that is the layers model.  In this post you'll learn why we need]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend Reading — 👋 Fan theory]]></title>
        <id>632f66c92dafe30b3489b528</id>
        <link href="https://labnotes.org/weekend-reading-fan-theory/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T00:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we get over our jet lag, have a git together, reverse engineer prompts at the Louvre, and even more Apple Watch workouts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Assaf Arkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[find() vs filter() in JavaScript – Differences Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/find-vs-filter-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/find-vs-filter-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T22:22:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A common interview question that JavaScript developers often get asked is to explain the difference between the find() and filter() methods.  In this tutorial today, I'll walk you through what these methods are and when you should use them. What is the filter() method? This method returns all the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aman Kalra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Copy Text to the Clipboard with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/copy-text-to-clipboard-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/copy-text-to-clipboard-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T21:18:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building advanced web pages and applications, you'll sometimes want to add the copy feature. This lets your users simply click a button or icon to copy text rather than highlighting the text and clicking a couple of buttons on the keyboard. This feature is mostly used when someone]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Add to an Array – JS Append]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-add-to-an-array-js-append/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-add-to-an-array-js-append/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T18:29:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use arrays in JavaScript to store a group of variables, often referred to as elements or items of the array. Each of these elements will have an index number assigned to them starting from zero.  By default, you can use the index of an element in an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UX vs UI – What's the Difference? Definition and Meaning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ux-vs-ui-whats-the-difference-definition-and-meaning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ux-vs-ui-whats-the-difference-definition-and-meaning/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T16:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing a website or an app, the finished product needs to be functional, intuitive, and aesthetically pleasing. This is where UX and UI design come in. UX and UI design are two technical terms that can often be confusing. Many people may use these two terms interchangeably, incorrectly, or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Developer Journey – How I Learned to Code with Dyslexia and ADHD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/developer-journey/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/developer-journey/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T16:01:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone, I'm Jalmari Ikävalko, a software developer in my early 30s. In this article, I’ll share my whole journey from my first contact with code to becoming the professional developer I am today.  I'll start from my childhood when I first got interested in programming. My Introduction to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jalmari Ikävalko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If at first your code doesn't succeed, `try`, `try` again?]]></title>
        <id>https://golangweekly.com/issues/432</id>
        <link href="https://golangweekly.com/issues/432"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#​432 — October 14, 2022


Unsubscribe  |  Read on the Web



    
Together with 
        
          
          
          
        
      

    
    

The Go Weekly Newsletter




  





  
  
Proposal: A try Statement for Error Handling? — Inspired by the results of the recent Go community survey, a self-proclaimed if err != nil expert(!) puts forward an interesting, well-written proposal for adding some tasty syntactic sugar to error handling. It’s only early days for this idea which may well not even pan out, but there’s plenty of room to jump in with your take on it and help push things forward.
Greg Weber 


  
  
Autostrada: A Codebase Generator for Go Projects — A site that lets you pick from a variety of options (webapp vs JSON API, SQLite vs Postgres – add auth, secure cookies, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Golang Weekly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Avoid Prop Drilling with the React Context API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/avoid-prop-drilling-with-react-context-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/avoid-prop-drilling-with-react-context-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T16:52:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The React Context API provides a way to pass data through multiple nested levels of components without having to manually pass that data to each level.  React context is one sure way of globally managing your data in your app, and it's a good way to avoid prop drilling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teenager Solves Stubborn Riddle About Prime Number Look-Alikes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=119742</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/teenager-solves-stubborn-riddle-about-prime-number-look-alikes-20221013/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T15:05:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In his senior year of high school, Daniel Larsen proved a key theorem about Carmichael numbers — strange entities that mimic the primes.            
The post Teenager Solves Stubborn Riddle About Prime Number Look-Alikes first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordana Cepelewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code a project three different ways (JavaScript + REST API + Database)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-project-three-different-ways-javascript-rest-api-database/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-project-three-different-ways-javascript-rest-api-database/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T14:06:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you code a similar project using different methods it helps you understand each method more. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to code a flight widget in JavaScript using multiple methods. First you will learn to create the project using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Machine Learning Model in Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-machine-learning-model-in-rust/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-machine-learning-model-in-rust/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T22:31:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning is a really interesting concept in computer programming. It involves using data to train a computer program to carry out tasks.  During the process, the program learns from data by discovering patterns. This reduces the need for programmers to hard code rules in some applications. Languages like]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chigozie Oduah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Email Alias – How to Set Up a Professional Email for Free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/email-alias-set-up-a-professional-email-for-free/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/email-alias-set-up-a-professional-email-for-free/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T22:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I needed to log in to AWS. But my main email address was rejected. Apparently I'd done this in the past and the account had been irreversibly deleted.  No reset option – just a message saying the account was permanently deleted: There are about a million ways to get]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Visualization Tools – 2022 Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-visualization-tools-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-visualization-tools-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T17:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data visualization is the process of interpreting or representing data graphically. Generally, it is the graphical or visual representation of data using charts, tables, histograms, and other info-graphics.  Data plays a major role in any type of organization. Data visualization helps us understand certain trends and insights, and make]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Human Brains Are Hard to Study. He Grows Useful Substitutes.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=119632</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/human-brains-are-hard-to-study-sergiu-pasca-grows-useful-substitutes-20221012/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T15:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With stem cell technology and lab-grown brain organoids, Sergiu Paşca seeks the causes of autism and other neuropsychiatric conditions.            
The post Human Brains Are Hard to Study. He Grows Useful Substitutes. first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Claudia Dreifus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lab-Grown Human Cells Form Working Circuits in Rat Brains]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=119651</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/lab-grown-human-cells-form-working-circuits-in-rat-brains-20221012/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T15:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Letting human brain organoids grow in animal brains could be an ethical new option for experimental studies of neurological disorders.            
The post Lab-Grown Human Cells Form Working Circuits in Rat Brains first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison Whitten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Docker and Kubernetes – Free Hands-On Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-docker-and-kubernetes-hands-on-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-docker-and-kubernetes-hands-on-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker and Kubernetes are important technologies that can help you scale your applications. Docker is a platform for packaging, deploying, and running applications in containers. Kubernetes is a system for managing containerized applications across a cluster of nodes. It provides basic mechanisms for deployment, maintenance, and scaling of applications. We]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement a Whitelist in Smart Contracts (ERC-721 NFT, ERC-1155, and others)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-whitelist-in-smartcontracts-erc-721-nft-erc-1155-and-others/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-whitelist-in-smartcontracts-erc-721-nft-erc-1155-and-others/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I will show you three ways you can create a whitelist in a smart contract. Here's what we'll discuss:  * On-chain whitelists  * Digital signatures  * Merkle trees All methods are available in the repo here [https://github.com/gapon2401/smartcontract-whitelist]. A whitelist is useful if you want]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Igor Gaponov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Web Storage Works – Local vs Session Storage Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-web-storage-works/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-web-storage-works/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone who works with the web needs to store data for a later use. Backend developers have some powerful databases in their toolkit. But if you are a frontend developer, you can still store and process data using web storage. In this article, you'll learn what is a web storage,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tooba Jamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Database Management Systems and SQL – Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dbms-and-sql-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dbms-and-sql-basics/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T13:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Database Management Systems and SQL are two of the most important and widely used tools on the internet today.  You use a Database Management System (DBMS) to store the data you collect from various sources, and SQL to manipulate and access the particular data you want in an efficient]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bikash Daga (Jain)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your Personal Brand as a Freelance Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/branding-for-developer-freelancers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/branding-for-developer-freelancers/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T13:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You probably didn’t get into freelance development to become a marketer.  You got into freelancing so you could work when you want, make more money, and control your life. But, if you haven’t realized it yet, building a career as a freelancer requires you to embrace more than just]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Cruz Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Webshop with Angular, Node.js, TypeScript, & Stripe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-webshop-with-angular-node-js-typescript-stripe/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-webshop-with-angular-node-js-typescript-stripe/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T13:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to build a webshop from scratch! We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build a webshop or e-commerce store using Angular/TypeScript, Express.js, and Stripe.  You will learn how to use Angular material and Tailwind to structure the UI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Recognize a Phishing Email – And What to Do When You Get One]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-recognize-phishing-email/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-recognize-phishing-email/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T00:52:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know the drill: you open your email client and there is it an email saying that you will be in trouble if you do not follow certain instructions in short time, no questions asked. All it takes is a single click, and you're in trouble. This kind of email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix TypeError: Cannot read Property 'push' of Undefined in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fix-typeerror-cannot-read-property-push-of-undefined-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fix-typeerror-cannot-read-property-push-of-undefined-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T23:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with JavaScript arrays, you have to be careful that you are not calling the push(), pop(), shift(), unShift(), or splice() methods on a variable that is meant to be an array but has a value of undefined. If you mistakenly do this, you'll get this error: If you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Free Resources to Learn Golang – Go Coding Courses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-resources-to-learn-golang-for-free/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-resources-to-learn-golang-for-free/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T23:11:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Golang has been around for a while now, and it's become quite popular among developers. It is a simple yet compelling programming language that's well-loved because of its powerful features like concurrency and the fact that it is developed by Google. Golang is a server-side language that's used in many]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Avdhoot Fulsundar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Programming Tips to Help You Level Up Your Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-programming-tips/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-programming-tips/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T19:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python is one of the most popular programming languages out there today. Its simplicity and readability make it a favorite among many programmers. So in this tutorial, I'm sharing a few pointers and strategies to help you improve your Python programming skills. How to Reverse a String in Python In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Fagbuyiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do You Prove a Secret?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=119593</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/how-to-prove-you-know-a-secret-without-giving-it-away-20221011/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T15:10:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zero-knowledge proofs allow researchers to prove their knowledge without divulging the knowledge itself.
            
The post How Do You Prove a Secret? first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sheon Han</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning Highlights a Hidden Order in Scents]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=119564</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/ai-model-links-smell-molecules-with-metabolic-processes-20221010/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T13:54:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Efforts to build a better digital “nose” suggest that our perception of scents reflects both the structure of aromatic molecules and the metabolic processes that make them.            
The post Machine Learning Highlights a Hidden Order in Scents first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison Parshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Weekly #82 (#blogPost)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/web-weekly-82/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/web-weekly-82/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Guten Tag, my friend!

Have you ever wondered if the Largest Contentful Paint metric measures unimportant things? Or do you know that some ARIA attributes aren't considered by translation tools? Or that there's a CSS property to avoid reflows when your content grows so that you need a scrollbar?
All the answers and much more are included in this week's Web Weekly. 🙈 Enjoy!
Welcome to the 19 new subscribers! I'm super excited to have you around! 👋
💡 Thought of the week

MDN is probably the most important webdev resource out there. It's THE documentation of the web. And while most of us only read it, you can contribute, too.
For example, if you find some outdated browser support information, head over to the "mdn/browser-compat-data" repo and propose an update! It's all structured JSON fi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript Generics – Use Case and Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typescript-generics-use-case-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typescript-generics-use-case-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T20:49:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn the basics of generics in TypeScript. We'll discuss how to use them and when they're useful in your code. Use Case for Generics Let's start with a simple example, where you want to print the value of an argument passed: function printData(data: number) {]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aman Kalra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Check if a String Contains a Substring in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-check-if-a-string-contains-a-substring-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-check-if-a-string-contains-a-substring-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T18:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with a JavaScript program, you might need to check whether a string contains a substring. A substring is a string inside another string. Specifically, you might need to check whether a word contains a specific character or a specific set of characters. Thankfully, there are a few]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does Recursion Work? Simplified in JavaScript with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/recursion-in-javascript-simplified/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/recursion-in-javascript-simplified/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T17:51:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recursion works similarly to how loops do in JavaScript. Loops allow you to execute a set of code multiple times as long as a condition is true. In this article, I will explain what Recursion is and how it works in JavaScript. In loops, when the condition becomes false, the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The hills are alive with the sound of gophers]]></title>
        <id>https://golangweekly.com/issues/431</id>
        <link href="https://golangweekly.com/issues/431"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#​431 — October 7, 2022


Unsubscribe  |  Read on the Web



    
Together with 
        
          
          
          
        
      

    
    

The Go Weekly Newsletter




  





  
  
How Do You Solve a Problem Like for Loop Variables? — Russ Cox began a discussion about what changes could be made to Go to resolve a tripping point around per-iteration vs per-loop binding of variables in loops – an issue first raised five years ago and common enough to be in Go’s FAQ. 
It's more complicated than you might think and this discussion provides a lot of insight, including from a C# core developer who shares how C# handled the same issue.
Russ Cox 


  
  
How a Bank Migrated Its Monorepo Seamlessly from Dep to Modules — While modules aren’t exactly new anymore, there are still quite a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Golang Weekly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python For Beginners Courses Ranked from Best to Worst – freeCodeCamp Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-python-courses-ranked-from-best-to-worst/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-python-courses-ranked-from-best-to-worst/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T19:54:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Does freeCodeCamp really need yet another Python course?   Click for answer.  Between the curriculum and the YouTube channel, freeCodeCamp has quite a few Python programming courses. But which Python course should you take? In this article, I'll rank every singe freeCodeCamp beginner's Python course from best to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Stack Data Structure to Solve Coding Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/stack-data-structure-solve-coding-challenges/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/stack-data-structure-solve-coding-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T18:48:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stack data structure is used frequently in programming, sometimes behind-the-scenes. And questions involving the stack data structure are very common in coding interviews. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use the stack data structure to solve the type of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Monumental’ Math Proof Solves Triple Bubble Problem and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=119509</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/monumental-math-proof-solves-triple-bubble-problem-and-more-20221006/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T16:54:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decades-old Sullivan’s conjecture, about the best way to minimize the surface area of a bubble cluster, was thought to be out of reach for three bubbles and up — until a new breakthrough result.            
The post ‘Monumental’ Math Proof Solves Triple Bubble Problem and More first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erica Klarreich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Implode – Convert Array to String with Join]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/php-implode-convert-array-to-string-with-join/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/php-implode-convert-array-to-string-with-join/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T16:14:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In PHP, the implode() function is a built-in function that takes an array and converts it to a string. implode() doesn’t modify the original array. It doesn’t matter whether the array is an indexed or associative array. Once you pass in the array to implode(), it joins all the values]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn PyTorch for Deep Learning – Free 26-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-pytorch-for-deep-learning-in-day/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-pytorch-for-deep-learning-in-day/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T14:48:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My comprehensive PyTorch course is now live on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel.   * You can view the full 26 hour course here [https://youtu.be/V_xro1bcAuA].  * Read the course materials online for free at learnpytorch.io    [https://learnpytorch.io/].  * See all of the course materials on GitHub]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Bourke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React Helmet – With Example Use Case]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-helmet-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-helmet-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T16:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because of the nature of single page applications (SPAs), modifying metadata in React apps can be tricky without using a helper library. Lucky for us, that library already exists – and it's called React Helmet. Leveraging Helmet for metadata inclusion can significantly simplify the process of making a React app SEO]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VLOOKUP in Excel – Formula and Example Function]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vlookup-in-excel-formula-and-example-function/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vlookup-in-excel-formula-and-example-function/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T16:26:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Excel, VLOOKUP() means vertical lookup. It is a powerful built-in function you can use to quickly search for a value in a spreadsheet. VLOOKUP() searches for a value in a vertical manner across the sheet – unlike the HLOOKUP() function which does it horizontally. Before using VLOOKUP(), make sure]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Functions Tutorial – IIFE, Function Parameters, and Code Blocks Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-function-iife-parameters-code-blocks-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-function-iife-parameters-code-blocks-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T16:06:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Functions are one of the most widely-used features in programming. So, it helps to have a solid understanding of how they work. This tutorial discusses everything you need to know to use JavaScript functions like a pro. Table of Contents  1.  What Is a Function?  2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi Sofela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big O Cheat Sheet – Time Complexity Chart]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/big-o-cheat-sheet-time-complexity-chart/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/big-o-cheat-sheet-time-complexity-chart/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T15:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An algorithm is a set of well-defined instructions for solving a specific problem. You can solve these problems in various ways. This means that the method you use to arrive at the same solution may differ from mine, but we should both get the same result. Because there are various]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Validate your Machine Learning Models Using TensorFlow Model Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-validate-machine-learning-models-with-tensorflow-model-analysis/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-validate-machine-learning-models-with-tensorflow-model-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T14:37:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My first deployed Machine Learning model was a failure. It was a simple Diabetes Diagnosis Model for potential diabetes mellitus patients – and quite frankly, I was beyond excited on deployment.  But the excitement soon disappeared when I received feedback from users. Simply put, the users felt the model]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salim Oyinlola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Molecule-Building Innovators Win Nobel Prize in Chemistry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=119285</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/molecule-building-innovators-win-2022-chemistry-nobel-prize-20221005/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T10:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The chemists Carolyn Bertozzi, Morten Meldal and K. Barry Sharpless were recognized for their development of click chemistry and bioorthogonal chemistry.            
The post Molecule-Building Innovators Win Nobel Prize in Chemistry first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yasemin Saplakoglu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF)? Laravel Web Security Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/laravel-web-security-csrf/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/laravel-web-security-csrf/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T21:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn about Laravel web security and how to secure your web applications and protect them from Cross-Site Request Forgery, or CSRF attacks. CSRF is a malicious activity that involves an attacker performing actions on behalf of an authenticated user. Fortunately, Laravel provides out-of-the-box measures to prevent]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sule-Balogun Olanrewaju Ganiu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Print Function in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-does-print-work-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-does-print-work-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T21:16:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Often, you'll need to print something to the console output when you're coding in Java. And the first thing that likely comes to your mind is the print function or print statement. But very few people know about the three different print functions/statements in Java. In this article, I am]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Architect a Full-Stack Application from Start to Finish]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-full-stack-application-from-start-to-finish/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-full-stack-application-from-start-to-finish/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T17:49:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software architecture is a massive topic. That said, I think I can give you a simple method you can use to approach the architecture of a full-stack application.  In particular, I want to talk about the order in which you should think about and build out the pieces of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Wagner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your First Microsoft 365 Application in 10 minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-microsoft-365-application-in-10-minutes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-microsoft-365-application-in-10-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T17:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a web developer and work with an organization that uses Microsoft 365, or you build applications that you sell to customers, I've got great news for you: you can use your existing skills to build applications that integrate with Microsoft 365. What's Microsoft 365? Microsoft 365 [https://www.microsoft.com/microsoft-365] is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Waldek Mastykarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Subquery – How to Sub Query in SELECT Statement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-subquery-how-to-sub-query-in-select-statement/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-subquery-how-to-sub-query-in-select-statement/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T17:08:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A SQL subquery is a query inside a query. So, in SQL, a subquery is also called a nested query or an inner query. The outer query in which the inner query is inserted is the main query. SQL admins usually use subqueries inside the WHERE clause to narrow down]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docker vs Virtual Machine (VM) – Key Differences You Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/docker-vs-vm-key-differences-you-should-know/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/docker-vs-vm-key-differences-you-should-know/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T16:48:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, you'll learn the differences between a virtual machine and a  Docker container. Both virtual machines and containers help replicate the development environment, and manage dependencies and configurations better. But there are certain differences you should be aware of that will help you choose a VM or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bala Priya C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Python by Thinking in Types]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-python-by-thinking-in-types/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-python-by-thinking-in-types/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T15:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you check Instagram today or watch YouTube? Well, you used a Python-based application! Python is one of the most popular programming languages. We just published a new Python course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. We have quite a few Python courses on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel so you may]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pioneering Quantum Physicists Win Nobel Prize in Physics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=119287</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/pioneering-quantum-physicists-win-nobel-prize-in-physics-20221004/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T09:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alain Aspect, John Clauser and Anton Zeilinger have won the 2022 Nobel Prize in Physics for groundbreaking experiments with entangled particles.            
The post Pioneering Quantum Physicists Win Nobel Prize in Physics first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Charlie Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Modal with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-modal-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-modal-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T23:49:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's probably happened to you before: you unintentionally attempted to perform an action on a webpage, but luckily got a pop-up window asking you to confirm your decision. This pop-up window is called a modal. It's a web page element that pops up and displays in front of other page]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Eke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is rem in CSS? rem Unit Font Size, Padding, Height, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-rem-in-css-rem-unit-font-size-padding-height-and-more/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-rem-in-css-rem-unit-font-size-padding-height-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T22:57:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rem measurement unit is a relative unit that you can use for length values in CSS. I will explain what this unit is, and how it is different from other units in this article. In my previous article, I explained the two categories of units in CSS: Absolute and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Your Jupyter Notebook into a User-Friendly Web App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-web-app-with-flask/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-web-app-with-flask/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T22:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being able to build predictive models is a superpower – but you can't make much of these models if users can't use them.  In this article, we will go through the process of building and deploying a machine learning web app using Flask and PythonAnywhere.  Flask is a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tooba Jamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use map(), filter(), and reduce() in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/map-filter-reduce-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/map-filter-reduce-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T22:06:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to learn React, it's important to get a fair understanding of some core JavaScript concepts first.  So if that's what you're doing, first of all – great job! You have made a wise decision by not starting directly with React.  Second, React builds on key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bhavesh Rawat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy a React Router App to Netlify and Fix the "Page Not Found" Error]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-a-routed-react-app-to-netlify/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-a-routed-react-app-to-netlify/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T17:16:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever experienced a “PAGE NOT FOUND” error when trying to access or refresh an application that uses React Router? Don't worry, you're not alone. In this article, you will learn how to deploy a React application that uses react-router without any problems. The Problem with Deploying react-router Apps]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Geneticist Awarded Nobel Prize for Studies of Extinct Human Ancestors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=119283</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/extinct-human-genomes-studies-win-nobel-prize-for-medicine-2022-20221003/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T09:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Svante Pääbo has been awarded the 2022 Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine for studying our extinct ancestors’ DNA.            
The post Geneticist Awarded Nobel Prize for Studies of Extinct Human Ancestors first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yasemin Saplakoglu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Weekly #81 (#blogPost)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/web-weekly-81/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/web-weekly-81/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-01T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Guten Tag, my friend!

Do you know that VS Code has a built-in version control system outside of Git? Or that SVG filters can be inlined in CSS? Or that you can soon find all render-blocking resources via JavaScript?
All the answers and much more are included in this week's Web Weekly. 🙈 Enjoy!
Welcome to the 44 new subscribers! I'm super excited to have you around! 👋
Thought of the week

As you may know, I like making lists. 🙈
My blog includes multiple link lists, and even my most successful open source project, Tiny Helpers, is just a public list.
Whenever I feel something could be valuable in the future, I just have the urge to put it somewhere. I might need it, right? One could also say this newsletter is just that — a list.
And even though I tried Obsidian and Notion, none of these…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to find all render-blocking resources with JavaScript (#blogPost)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/how-to-find-all-render-blocking-resources-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/how-to-find-all-render-blocking-resources-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fast websites are good, right? Nobody likes to wait, and with Core Web Vitals being a ranking factor, optimizing performance is more critical than ever.
Rightfully, one of the main Core Web Vitals is Largest Contentful Paint which measures when elements are rendered and become visible on screen. But how hard could it be to render things quickly?
When it's coming to render time, it's critical to consider what resources you load and how you load them. Render-blocking resources are a primary reason for slow and delayed rendering. Stylesheets and synchronous scripts are the most common offenders.
Unfortunately, there hasn't been a straightforward way to discover render-blocking resources. And even though you could always rely on tools such as ct.css to find problematic resources, these tools r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Almanac Highlights 2022 (#blogPost)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/web-almanac-highlights-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/web-almanac-highlights-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following my three-year-old tradition, I spent the last few days reading and summarizing HTTP Archive's yearly Web Almanac on Twitter. As usual, the folks behind it put together a comprehensive report on the state of the web, backed by real data analyzed by trusted web experts.
It's a fantastic resource to understand the current web technology landscape and discover new web platform features.
If you're curious, here are the previous summaries:
Highlights 2019
Highlights 2020
Highlights 2021
2022 Web Almanac highlights

I won't summarize the entire mega-thread here, so head over to Twitter to read it entirely if you're curious.

        

        
Stefan Judis
              @stefanjudis
            
.@HTTPArchive's annual state of the web report — the Web Almanac — is out! 
As every year, I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeError: only size-1 arrays can be converted to Python scalars]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fix-typeerror-only-size-1-arrays-can-be-converted-to-python-scalars/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fix-typeerror-only-size-1-arrays-can-be-converted-to-python-scalars/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T21:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, you can use the numpy library when working with arrays and certain math concepts like matrices and linear algebra.  But like every other aspect of learning and working with a programming language, errors are unavoidable.  In this article, you'll learn how to fix the "TypeError: only]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Absolute and Relative Units in CSS? Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/absolute-and-relative-css-units/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/absolute-and-relative-css-units/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T21:19:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In CSS, we categorize measurement units as either absolute or relative units. In this article, I'll explain what these categories are with examples of units that fall under each of them. CSS Measurement Units You can use different measurement units in CSS. You use these units with length or size]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rename a File in Linux – Bash Terminal Command]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rename-file-linux-bash-command/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rename-file-linux-bash-command/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T15:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Renaming files is a very common operation whether you are using the command line or the GUI.  Compared to the GUI (or Graphical User Interface), the CLI is especially powerful. This is in part because you can rename files in bulk or even schedule the scripts to rename files]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DNS Server Not Responding – How to Fix the Error in Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fix-dns-server-not-responding-error-windows-10/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fix-dns-server-not-responding-error-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T15:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think it's safe to say that the vast majority of professionals depend on the internet these days.  So being denied access to the internet when you are trying to mine nuggets of valuable information from your go-to web sites can be quite an ordeal. Especially when you are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gavin Lon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the DOM? A Behind-the-Scenes Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-dom-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-dom-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T14:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding how the DOM and events work in JavaScript is key if you want to be an effective front end developer. In this article, you'll learn what the DOM is and how it works. What is the DOM? DOM stands for Document Object Model. It's the interface between JavaScript and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Star Trek’s Lieutenant Uhura Overcame Astronomical Odds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=119316</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/how-star-treks-lieutenant-uhura-overcame-astronomical-odds-20220930/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T13:26:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Readers rescued a Star Trek crew from a probabilistic predicament armed only with the power of mathematical reasoning.            
The post How Star Trek’s Lieutenant Uhura Overcame Astronomical Odds first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pradeep Mutalik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four years of quiet Go improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://golangweekly.com/issues/430</id>
        <link href="https://golangweekly.com/issues/430"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#​430 — September 30, 2022


Unsubscribe  |  Read on the Web



The Go Weekly Newsletter




  





  
  
What's New in Go's Runtime: Four Years Later — It’s always fantastic to get a roundup from the core Go team on their progress, and while Go 1.13 through 1.18 have certainly seen their fair share of enhancements, we also get to learn a bit more about Go 1.19’s memory limit feature and improved garbage collection. Some highlights from the past few years:


Big efficiency gains on multicore systems.
Go's scheduler spends up to 30% less CPU time spinning.
Go's GC limits its CPU use when the app is idle, reducing CPU spikes.
defer-red function calls now cost as little as regular function calls (mostly).
More efficient timer management.
Michael Knyszek 


  
  
Automatically Detect and Trac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Golang Weekly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Swap Two Array Elements in JavaScript – Switch Elements in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/swap-two-array-elements-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/swap-two-array-elements-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T20:15:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with arrays, there are times when you need to swap two elements in an array in JavaScript. Maybe you're working on an algorithm question such as the bubble sort algorithm where you need to compare two values and then swap them if your condition is true. Aside]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Authentication vs Authorization – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/whats-the-difference-between-authentication-and-authorisation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/whats-the-difference-between-authentication-and-authorisation/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T17:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're starting out in web development, you'll likely hear the terms authentication and authorization all the time. And it doesn't help that they're both usually abbreviated 'auth', so it's very easy to get the two confused. In this article, you will learn:  * The differences between authentication and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Weatherston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bubble Sort – Algorithm in Java, C++, Python with Example Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/bubble-sort-algorithm-in-java-cpp-python-with-example-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/bubble-sort-algorithm-in-java-cpp-python-with-example-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T17:34:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bubble sort is a type of sorting algorithm you can use to arrange a set of values in ascending order. If you want, you can also implement bubble sort to sort the values in descending order. A real-world example of a bubble sort algorithm is how the contact list on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Selectors – Cheat Sheet for Class, Name, Child Selector List]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-selectors-cheat-sheet-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-selectors-cheat-sheet-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T15:22:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS selectors target and select the HTML elements you want to style. Specifically, CSS selectors allow you to select multiple elements at once. They are helpful when you want to apply the same styles to more than one HTML element, because you will not repeat yourself by writing the same]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What We Know About Monkeypox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=119250</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/epidemiologist-what-we-know-about-monkeypox-20220929/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T14:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even though we’ve learned a lot about this relative of smallpox, some mysteries remain due to a lack of political will.            
The post What We Know About Monkeypox first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara C. Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Low-Code Ecommerce App with Stripe, Postgres, & REST API Backend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-low-code-ecommerce-app-with-stripe-postgres-rest-api-backend/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-low-code-ecommerce-app-with-stripe-postgres-rest-api-backend/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T13:43:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building apps can be much quicker with low-code tools. A low-code platform can give you pre-built UI components packed with functionality like tables, buttons, and text inputs. This allows you to skip the frontend templates and build your own quickly. We just published a tutorial on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parameters vs Arguments in JavaScript – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-the-difference-between-parameters-and-arguments-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-the-difference-between-parameters-and-arguments-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T21:18:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is one of the most popular programming languages out there for web development. The dynamic values passed in a JavaScript function can change when the function gets called in another location in the code. The keywords we use to name these data are parameters and arguments, but some developers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Segun Ajibola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code a 2D Game Using JavaScript, HTML, and CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-a-2d-game-using-javascript-html-and-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-a-2d-game-using-javascript-html-and-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T19:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript can be a surprisingly good programming language to use for creating 2D games. Especially games you want to be playable on almost any device.  We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to code a 2D game using JavaScript, HTML, CSS,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biologists Use Genetic Circuits to Program Plant Roots]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=119210</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/biologists-use-genetic-circuits-to-program-plant-roots-20220928/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T13:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using inserted genetic circuitry, synthetic biologists controlled the growth of plant roots for the first time.            
The post Biologists Use Genetic Circuits to Program Plant Roots first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joanna Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Test Your Express.js and Mongoose Apps with Jest and SuperTest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-test-in-express-and-mongoose-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-test-in-express-and-mongoose-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T23:26:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Testing is a vital part of software development. The sooner you start testing, the better.  In this article, I'll show you how to write tests for your NodeJs/ExpressJS and MongoDB/Mongoose applications with Jest and Supertest. Let's get started First let's set up a demo Express.js app. Let's say we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rakesh Potnuru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js Server-Side JavaScript – What is Node Used For?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/node-js-server-side-javascript-what-is-node-used-for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/node-js-server-side-javascript-what-is-node-used-for/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T21:34:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release of Node.js in 2009 by Ryan Dahl increased the scope of what developers could do with JavaScript. Prior to that, you could only use JavaScript on the client side (the browser) or frontend of web applications. With Node.js, developers can create server side applications, command line tools, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Command Line Interface – for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-cli-beginner-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-cli-beginner-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T21:11:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a lot to learn when you're getting into tech. But fortunately there are some skills that you can use across different programming languages, operating systems, and tools.  And knowing how to use the command line interface (also known as the command prompt or terminal, depending on your operating]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maybell Obadoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Debug Your Python Code with the Python Debugger (pdb)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/debugging-in-python-using-pdb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/debugging-in-python-using-pdb/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T17:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging tools are at the heart of any programming language. And as a developer, it's hard to make progress and write clean code unless you know your way around these tools. This article will help you get acquainted with one such tool: The Python Debugger (pdb) [https://docs.python.org/3/library/pdb.html#:~:text=The%20module%20pdb%20defines%20an,context%20of%20any%20stack%20frame] Note that this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jagruti Tiwari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Vertical Scrolling in React Using react-router-hash-link]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-vertical-scrolling-in-react-using-react-router-hash-link/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-vertical-scrolling-in-react-using-react-router-hash-link/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T17:42:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smooth scrolling is a feature that makes webpages more usable and allows for a better user scrolling experience in most browsers. Implementing a smooth page scroll while using react-router-dom has been a problem in React.js. So this article, you are going to learn how to implement smooth vertical scrolling using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Information Systems? Definition for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-information-systems-definition-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-information-systems-definition-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T16:43:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have heard the term "information systems" as a type of degree some people get from a college or university. Or maybe you've heard it as a general term used to describe information and communication systems in general. Information systems are more than a degree or a general term.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Big Is Infinity?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=119076</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/how-big-is-infinity-20220927/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T15:48:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Of all the endless questions children and mathematicians have asked about infinity, one of the most fascinating has to do with its size.            
The post How Big Is Infinity? first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Honner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Java Programming (version 17)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-java-programming/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-java-programming/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T13:37:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Java has been one of the most popular programming languages for a long time. It is considered a general-purpose, concurrent, strongly typed, class-based object-oriented language. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you the Java programming language. This course is perfect for beginners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux for Hackers – Basics for Cybersecurity Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linux-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linux-basics/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T23:20:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time to learn how to use the operating system of the average hacker 🐧. In this article, we will take a little tour of:  * The Linux operating system  * Package management  * The Linux file structure  * The Command Line Interface And you get to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Iwugo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript For loop – How to Loop Through an Array in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-loop-through-an-array-with-for-loop-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-loop-through-an-array-with-for-loop-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T23:14:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A loop is an instruction in computer programming that allows an application to repeat a process until a specific condition is met. For example, say you want to run through a list of names and output each name on your screen. If you didn't use a loop, you'd end up]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dennis Temoye Charity</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iteration in Golang – How to Loop Through Data Structures in Go]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/iteration-in-golang/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/iteration-in-golang/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T22:44:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In programming, iteration (commonly known as looping) is a process where a step is repeated n number of times until a specific condition is met. Just like every other programming language, Golang has a way of iterating through different data structures and data types like structs, maps, arrays, strings, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubaydah Abdulwasiu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Serverless Logic with Azure Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-serverless-logic-with-azure-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-serverless-logic-with-azure-functions/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Serverless Computing? You can think of serverless computing as a function as a service, or a microservice that is hosted on a cloud platform.  In this setup, your business logic runs as functions, and you do not have to manually create or scale infrastructure. The cloud platform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salim Oyinlola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An app to open your current finder directory in VS Code (#note)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/notes/an-app-to-open-your-current-finder-directory-in-vs-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/notes/an-app-to-open-your-current-finder-directory-in-vs-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just discovered the OpenInCode app. I'm not sure yet if I'll really use it, but I like the idea of a having a quick way to open a directory in VS Code with a single click.
The app is a little outdated and wonky but it works.
First, the documenation is outdated: to install the app, use the following brew command.
brew install --cask open-in-code

Follow the README instructions and you're good to go. There's a little issue with macOS dark mode but I can live with this.
Let's see if I'll use it. 😉


          
          
            Reply to Stefan]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript Concepts You Should Know Before Learning React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-concepts-you-should-know-before-learning-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-concepts-you-should-know-before-learning-react/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T19:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is one of the most popular JavaScript frameworks for building single page applications. Needless to say, as a JavaScript framework, it requires you to have a good knowledge of JavaScript concepts. In this article, we are going to take a look at some of those JavaScript concepts that you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Mishra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning for Everybody]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-for-everybody/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-for-everybody/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T17:28:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning technology is now so common that you probably use it dozens of times a day without even realizing it. And since it has so many applications, the job prospects are great for anyone with a lot of machine learning experience. We just released a machine learning course on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Physicists Rewrite a Quantum Rule That Clashes With Our Universe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=119061</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/physicists-rewrite-a-quantum-rule-that-clashes-with-our-universe-20220926/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T14:41:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The past and the future are tightly linked in conventional quantum mechanics. Perhaps too tightly. A tweak to the theory could let quantum possibilities increase as space expands.            
The post Physicists Rewrite a Quantum Rule That Clashes With Our Universe first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Charlie Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Drop-down Menu – How to Add a Drop-Down List with the Select Element]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-drop-down-menu-how-to-add-a-drop-down-list-with-the-select-element/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-drop-down-menu-how-to-add-a-drop-down-list-with-the-select-element/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T14:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many websites, applications, and web pages use drop-down menus to help display a list of information. You can use them to create navigation menus, options for forms, and more. If you're looking at some of these menus or lists, you might imagine how complex creating them could be. And yes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Git and GitHub – Introduction for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-git-and-github/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-git-and-github/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T05:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git and GitHub are common tools used in programming. They help you manage different versions of your code and collaborate with other developers. Building projects is one of the core parts of being a developer. And Git and GitHub are essential tools you'll use when building projects with others. But]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Segun Ajibola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Weekly #80 (#blogPost)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/web-weekly-80/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/web-weekly-80/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-24T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Guten Tag, my friend!

Do you know that with Safari 16 (released September 12), three long-awaited browser features are now cross-browser supported? Or that CSS provides a way to style language-specific quotation characters? Oooooor, why the CSS url() function doesn't work with custom properties?
All the answers and much more are included in this week's Web Weekly. 🙈 Enjoy!
And before we get started, welcome to the 91 new subscribers! I'm super excited to have you around! 👋
3k subscribers, webweekly.email and the noonies

On a personal note: so many exciting things happened last week!
First, this tiny newsletter passed 3000 subscribers! 🎉 It's absurd that 3000 people receive an email from me weekly. Thank you all for reading along!
Second, motivated by all this, I finally took the time …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend Reading — 👋 0.1 + 0.2]]></title>
        <id>63265fbf2667443708169345</id>
        <link href="https://labnotes.org/weekend-reading-0-1-0-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-24T20:20:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we play Dungeon & Types, visualize our designs IRL, FOMO into the Metaverse, and wrestle a bear for a Belgium waffle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Assaf Arkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Background Image – How to Add Wallpaper Images to Your Website]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-background-image-how-to-add-wallpaper-images-to-your-website/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-background-image-how-to-add-wallpaper-images-to-your-website/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T19:18:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Background images can help beautify websites and make them more attractive to users.  In this article, you'll learn:   * How to add a background image to your website using the CSS background-image     property.   * Other CSS background properties for images. How]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use SurrealDb with the Fresh Framework and Deno]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-surrealdb-with-fresh-framework/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-surrealdb-with-fresh-framework/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T17:51:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SurrealDB is a newly launched database that has recently started gaining popularity in the programming world. SurrealDB was built with the Rust language and was created by Tobie Morgan Hitchcock [https://www.linkedin.com/in/tobiemorganhitchcock/] and Jaime Morgan Hitchcock [https://www.linkedin.com/in/jaimemorganhitchcock/]. SurrealDB's new database comes with many features, but I'm most interested in the Deno]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Sort a List Recursively in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-sort-recursively-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-sort-recursively-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T14:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you want to sort a list or array in Python, there are many sorting algorithms you can use.  Some use looping concepts like Insertion Sort, Bubble Sort, and Selection Sort. On the other hand, you can also sort the same list or array using Merge Sort with the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>P S Mohammed Ali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>