<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://daorren.github.io/osmofeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-04T02:12:29.629Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://daorren.github.io/osmofeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://daorren.github.io/osmofeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend Reading — Just hacks all the way down]]></title>
        <id>62b7a52fd9dbed2e26ec7107</id>
        <link href="https://labnotes.org/weekend-reading-just-hacks-all-the-way-down/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T00:39:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we ride on one and two half wheels, design a responsive snake, locate our headphones, and dance to the ring tone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Assaf Arkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Import SVGs in a React and Vite app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-import-svgs-in-react-and-vite/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-import-svgs-in-react-and-vite/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T22:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you having difficulties importing SVGs into your React app? This is a problem that many developers face, especially when setting up a new React app with a module bundler. In this article, I will share with you the different ways of importing SVGs in React, as well as how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Mitolu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript String Comparison – How to Compare Strings in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-comparison-how-to-compare-strings-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-comparison-how-to-compare-strings-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T22:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may want to compare two strings to know which is higher or lower alphabetically or to see if they are equal. You can do this in many ways. I'll show you two of them in this article. 1. How to Compare Strings Using localeCompare You can use the localeCompare]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Else-If Statement Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-else-if-statement-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-else-if-statement-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T22:02:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conditional statements are helpful for decision-making and are a core concept in all programming languages. In this article, you will learn how to write conditional statements in Python. Specifically, you will learn how to write if, if else, and elif (also known as  else if) statements in Python. Here]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Track Machine Learning Experiments with HarperDB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/track-machine-learning-experiments-with-harperdb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/track-machine-learning-experiments-with-harperdb/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T17:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Properly tracking your machine learning experiments is easier than you think. When working on a machine learning project, you will conduct different machine learning experiments before you reach the final ML model with the best performance.  Here are some possible machine learning experiments you might conduct:  * Testing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davis David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use VLOOKUP in Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-vlookup-in-excel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-vlookup-in-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T16:47:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working in Excel, the VLOOKUP function makes looking up information less time-consuming. This is particularly true when you're using more than one Excel sheet. In this article, you will learn what the VLOOKUP function does, as well as understand the syntax behind it. You will also learn how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Battery Icon Not Showing – How to Restore Missing Battery Icon in Windows PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/battery-icon-not-showing-how-to-restore-missing-battery-icon-in-windows-pc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/battery-icon-not-showing-how-to-restore-missing-battery-icon-in-windows-pc/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T15:57:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, you’re working with your Windows PC and you discover you can’t find the battery icon in the taskbar. You even expand hidden icons and you still can’t find the battery icon. This could result in a negative effect on your productivity – because if you don't plug your laptop]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Life Helps Make Almost Half of All Minerals on Earth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=116554</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/life-helps-make-almost-half-of-all-minerals-20220701/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T14:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new origins-based system for classifying minerals reveals the huge geochemical imprint that life has left on Earth. It could help us identify other worlds with life too.            
The post Life Helps Make Almost Half of All Minerals on Earth first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joanna Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The place to share your Go projects.]]></title>
        <id>https://golangweekly.com/issues/418</id>
        <link href="https://golangweekly.com/issues/418"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#​418 — July 1, 2022


Unsubscribe  |  Read on the Web



☺️ Somehow we've only just noticed that the go.dev site links to Golang Weekly in its footer — a big thank you to anyone involved in that decision. We're not an official Go newsletter by any means, but we try our best to live up to the ideals of the Go community and to reflect everything we see going on. Thanks to all of you for your ongoing support!
__
Peter Cooper and the Cooperpress team


    
    

The Go Weekly Newsletter




  





  
  
Awesome Go: Almost 2400 Categorized Go Resources — Every year we link to this fantastic resource because unlike many ‘awesome’ lists, it continues to get very frequent updates and you’re encouraged to submit contributions of your own too (but don't forget to send them to us too! 😉)
Awesome …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Golang Weekly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Set – How to Create Sets in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-set-how-to-create-sets-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-set-how-to-create-sets-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T22:43:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use sets in Python to store a collection of data in a single variable.  Each of the built-in data structures in Python like lists, dictionaries, and tuples have their distinguishing features.  Here are some of the features of sets in Python:   * Duplicate items]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Functions in JavaScript? A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-functions-in-javascript-a-beginners-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-functions-in-javascript-a-beginners-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T20:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Functions are one of the fundamental concepts in programming. They let us write concise, modular, reusable, and maintainable code. They also help us obey the DRY principle when writing code. In this article, you will learn what functions are in JavaScript, how to write your own custom functions, and how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chinwendu Enyinna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the React useState Hook in 10 minutes – Hooks for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-react-usestate-hook-in-10-minutes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-react-usestate-hook-in-10-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T19:40:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone 🌈 I haven't written about handling state in React for a long time. The last time was in this article [/news/get-pro-with-react-setstate-in-10-minutes-d38251d1c781/], four years ago, and it seems like it helped a lot of you. I received tons of views and amazing feedback, so thanks a lot – you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eduardo Vedes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Stay Motivated While Learning to Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-stay-motivated-while-learning-to-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-stay-motivated-while-learning-to-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T17:54:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning to code can be like preparing for a long battle. Ultimately, winning is not always determined by your initial strength, but by how well prepared you are and how long you can hold out.  With programming, the greatest challenge is often not the complexity of the language, but]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>D.M. Oladele</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sordid Past of the Cubic Formula]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=116369</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/the-scandalous-history-of-the-cubic-formula-20220630/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T14:54:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The quest to solve cubic equations led to duels, betrayals — and modern mathematics.            
The post The Sordid Past of the Cubic Formula first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David S. Richeson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Computers Be Mathematicians?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=116413</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/can-computers-be-mathematicians-20220629/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T21:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence has bested humans at problem-solving challenges like chess and Go. Is mathematics research next? Steven Strogatz speaks with mathematician Kevin Buzzard to learn about the effort to translate math into language that computers understand.            
The post Can Computers Be Mathematicians? first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Strogatz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Date Comparison – How to Compare Dates in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-date-comparison-how-to-compare-dates-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-date-comparison-how-to-compare-dates-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T19:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A date is one of the most common datatypes developers use when creating real-world applications.  But often, devs struggle with this datatype and end up using date libraries like Moment.js for simple tasks that aren't worth the large package size that comes with installing an entire package. In this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React + Ink CLI Tutorial – How to Build a Browser Command Line Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-js-ink-cli-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-js-ink-cli-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T18:41:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is a popular front-end JavaScript development library. It ranks #1 in awareness and usage according to the State Of JS 2021 [https://2021.stateofjs.com/en-US/libraries/front-end-frameworks/] survey.  This means that a majority of JavaScript developers likely are aware of or use React.  Even though React is popular for building web app]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amazing Enyichi Agu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Design an API – Application Programming Interface Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/design-an-api-application-program-interface/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/design-an-api-application-program-interface/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T18:04:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[API stands for Application Programming Interface. An API communicates with two applications using requests and responses. It is exposed to external users. How Does an API Work?  How an API worksImagine you are in a store and want to buy a soda. But you can't just walk in and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Iroegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Localhost? Local Host IP Address Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-localhost/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-localhost/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T16:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are an experienced web developer, then you’ve likely seen the term “localhost” on many occasions. And even if you’re a beginner and just getting started in web development, you might have seen the number “127.0.0.1:” while using a live server plugin. You might be using it to test]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript String to Date – Date Parsing in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-to-date-date-parsing-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-to-date-date-parsing-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T15:46:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dates are a pretty fundamental concept. We use them all the time. And computers use them all the time. But parsing dates using JavaScript can be a little...well, interesting. In this article, we'll:  1. Discuss date formatting  2. Turn a wee ol' string into a proper date object]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Controversy Continues Over Whether Hot Water Freezes Faster Than Cold]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=116307</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/does-hot-water-freeze-faster-than-cold-physicists-keep-asking-20220629/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T14:50:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decades after a Tanzanian teenager initiated study of the “Mpemba effect,” the effort to confirm or refute it is leading physicists toward new theories about how substances relax to equilibrium.            
The post Controversy Continues Over Whether Hot Water Freezes Faster Than Cold first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Mann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Terraform and Azure by Building a Dev Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-terraform-and-azure-by-building-a-dev-environment/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-terraform-and-azure-by-building-a-dev-environment/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T14:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform is an open source infrastructure as code software tool that makes it easy to programmatically to set up infrastructure on a variety of cloud service providers. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Terraform and Azure to setup a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Convert String to Number – JS String to Int Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-convert-string-to-number-js-string-to-int-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-convert-string-to-number-js-string-to-int-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T00:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with data from various sources, some of these data may arrive in the incorrect format. And you'll need to correct those formats before performing certain actions on the data.  This is just one of the many reasons you might want to learn how to convert a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Check if an Item is in an Array in JavaScript – JS Contains with Array.includes()]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/check-if-an-item-is-in-an-array-in-javascript-js-contains-with-array-includes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/check-if-an-item-is-in-an-array-in-javascript-js-contains-with-array-includes/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T22:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use the includes() method in JavaScript to check if an item exists in an array. You can also use it to check if a substring exists within a string.  It returns true if the item is found in the array/string and false if the item doesn't exist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Understand Complex Coding Concepts Using the Feynman Technique]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-understand-complex-coding-concepts-better-using-the-feynman-technique/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-understand-complex-coding-concepts-better-using-the-feynman-technique/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T19:26:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Feynman approach is an excellent way to gain a deeper understanding of a complex topic. It's one of the quickest ways to turn a complex topic into one that you can explain in simple terms to others. This article will teach you how to break complex coding concepts into]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CESS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Java in Ubuntu – JDK Linux Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-java-in-ubuntu-jdk-linux-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-java-in-ubuntu-jdk-linux-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T19:21:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Java is one of the most popular programming languages in use today. And a clean setup lets you seamlessly install Java and switch between different versions when you're building applications.  In this tutorial you will learn how to:  * Install any Java version,  * Switch between Java]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sigl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[429 Error – Too Many Requests HTTP Code Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-the-429-too-many-requests-http-error/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-the-429-too-many-requests-http-error/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T15:45:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you are a web developer or you are a regular internet user, you might have encountered a 429 error. It means that the website can't handle the number of requests being sent to it. For a developer, this error can be hard to resolve because, on many occasions, it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Greedy Algorithms and Solve Coding Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-greedy-algorithms/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-greedy-algorithms/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many tech companies want people to solve coding challenges during interviews and many of the challenges can be solved using a greedy algorithm. A greedy algorithm is any algorithm that follows the problem-solving heuristic of making the locally optimal choice at each stage.  We just published a course on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protein Blobs Linked to Alzheimer’s Affect Aging in All Cells]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=116232</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/protein-blobs-linked-to-alzheimers-affect-aging-in-all-cells-20220628/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T13:52:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Protein buildups like those seen around neurons in Alzheimer’s, Parkinson’s and other brain diseases occur in all aging cells, a new study suggests. Learning their significance may reveal new strategies for treating age-related diseases.            
The post Protein Blobs Linked to Alzheimer’s Affect Aging in All Cells first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Viviane Callier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write a Java Program to Get the Fibonacci Series]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-a-java-program-to-find-the-fibonacci-series/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-a-java-program-to-find-the-fibonacci-series/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T12:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fibonacci Series is a special kind of sequence that starts with 0 and 1, and every number after those two is the sum of the two preceding numbers.  The Fibonacci series goes like this: 0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, … and so on. It]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bikash Daga (Jain)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refresh the Page in JavaScript – JS Reload Window Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/refresh-the-page-in-javascript-js-reload-window-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/refresh-the-page-in-javascript-js-reload-window-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T17:41:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're developing applications like a blog or a page where the data may change based on user actions, you'll want that page to refresh frequently. When the page refreshes or reloads, it will show any new data based off those user interactions. Good news – you can implement this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn HTML – Responsive Web Design Study Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-responsive-web-design-study-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-responsive-web-design-study-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T16:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML (HyperText Markup Language) is an important markup language for building websites. HTML represents the content of the web page. But when you are learning this information for the first time, it can be hard to keep track of all of the different HTML elements.  In this article, I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NameError: Name plot_cases_simple is Not Defined – How to Fix this Python Error]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nameerror-name-plot_cases_simple-is-not-defined-how-to-fix-this-python-error/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nameerror-name-plot_cases_simple-is-not-defined-how-to-fix-this-python-error/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T15:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This first step in fixing a coding error is to understand the error. Although some error messages may seem confusing, most of them will help you fix the error.  In this article, we'll be talking about an error that falls under the NameError  category in Python. You'll see]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Clear a JavaScript Array – JS Empty Array]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-clear-a-javascript-array-js-empty-array/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-clear-a-javascript-array-js-empty-array/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T15:53:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are multiple ways to empty an existing array in JavaScript. Emptying an array means removing all values from it. In this article, I'll show and explain two ways to clear an array. 1. How to Clear an Array by Modifying the Length Property The length property of an array]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Weigh Truth With a Balance Scale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=116163</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/puzzles-on-weighing-truth-with-a-balance-scale-20220627/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T14:06:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recreational mathematics, the balance scale is an endless source of puzzles that require precise and elaborate logic and teach the fundamentals of generalization.            
The post How to Weigh Truth With a Balance Scale first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pradeep Mutalik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Weekly #70 (#blogPost)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/web-weekly-70/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/web-weekly-70/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy summer day!

I learned that Edge has been shipping the feature of vertical tabs for over a year now. Did you see people talking about it? I didn't.
This discovery made me look at my browsing habits, though. I use Firefox as my primary browser and have 88 open tabs while writing this newsletter.
Additionally, Wavebox sits on another monitor to move Gmail, multiple Messengers and all the other always-open websites out of my browser. This approach works, but I wouldn't say that I'm happy with this setup.
But it's not only me. I see a lot of folks fighting the unorganized mess of too many tabs and websites. Did the internet outgrow browsers built to show a handful of websites?
I read somewhere that Chrome's user base is so big that Google doesn't want to make drastic changes to the UI no…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend Reading — … no worries if not]]></title>
        <id>62ae7220d9dbed2e26ec6366</id>
        <link href="https://labnotes.org/weekend-reading-no-worries-if-not/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T00:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we walk through the airport, delete all French files, mediate on that text, and fail to guess the prompt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Assaf Arkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to create an API wrapper using a JavaScript proxy (#snippet)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/snippets/how-to-create-an-api-wrapper-using-a-javascript-proxy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/snippets/how-to-create-an-api-wrapper-using-a-javascript-proxy/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just found a super smart gist from David Wells that's worth bookmarking.
David uses a JavaScript Proxy to map object properties to fetch calls.
This approach works quite nice for querying RESTful APIs. apiObject.cars() maps to /cars/ and apiObject.cars('123') maps to /cars/123/. 👏
// Found at https://gist.github.com/DavidWells/53518b3c12344952641dc81cc7599939
const createApi = (url) => {
  return new Proxy({}, {
    get(target, key) {
      return async function(id = "") {
        const response = await fetch(`${url}/${key}/${id}`)
        if (response.ok) {
          return response.json();
        }
        return Promise.resolve({ error: "Malformed Request" })
      }
    }
  })
}

let api = createApi("https://swapi.co/api")

// 'get' request to https://swapi.co/api/people
let people = await api.people()

// 'get' request to https://swapi.co/api/people/1
let person = await api.people(1)

What a great little trick! 💯


          
          
            Reply to Stefan]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Static in Java? What does this keyword mean? [Solved]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-static-in-java-what-does-this-keyword-mean/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-static-in-java-what-does-this-keyword-mean/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-24T21:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use the static keyword in different parts of a Java program like variables, methods, and static blocks.  The main purpose of using the static keyword in Java is to save memory. When we create a variable in a class that will be accessed by other classes, we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Handle Missing Data in a Dataset]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-missing-data-in-a-dataset/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-missing-data-in-a-dataset/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-24T21:14:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Missing values are common when working with real-world datasets – not the cleaned ones available on Kaggle, for example.  Missing data could result from a human factor (for example, a person deliberately failing to respond to a survey question), a problem in electrical sensors, or other factors. And when]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ibrahim Abayomi Ogunbiyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perform Data Augmentation in NLP Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-perform-data-augmentation-in-nlp-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-perform-data-augmentation-in-nlp-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-24T15:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In machine learning, you need to have a large amount of data in order to achieve strong model performance.  Using a method known as data augmentation, you can create more data for your machine learning project. Data augmentation is a collection of techniques that manage the process of automatically]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davis David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Check if a JavaScript String is a Valid URL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/check-if-a-javascript-string-is-a-url/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/check-if-a-javascript-string-is-a-url/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-24T15:09:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A URL – or Uniform Resource Locator – is text used to identify resources like web pages, images, and videos on the internet. We commonly refer to URLs as website addresses, and they're used for file transfer, emails, and other applications. URLs consist of multiple parts – protocol, domain name, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikram Aruchamy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[By Exploring Virtual Worlds, AI Learns in New Ways]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=116176</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/ai-makes-strides-in-virtual-worlds-more-like-our-own-20220624/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-24T14:26:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intelligent beings learn by interacting with the world. Artificial intelligence researchers have adopted a similar strategy to teach their virtual agents new tricks.             
The post By Exploring Virtual Worlds, AI Learns in New Ways first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison Whitten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Low-Code Dashboard for Your Startup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-low-code-dashboard-for-your-startup/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-low-code-dashboard-for-your-startup/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-24T12:52:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a dashboard to keep track of customers and users is much easier than you may think. You can build an API-powered marketing dashboard using a low code approach.  We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create a dashboard to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuzzing: an introduction, plus updates coming to 1.19.]]></title>
        <id>https://golangweekly.com/issues/417</id>
        <link href="https://golangweekly.com/issues/417"/>
        <updated>2022-06-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#​417 — June 24, 2022


Unsubscribe  |  Read on the Web



The Go Weekly Newsletter




  





  
  
▶  An Introduction to Fuzzing in Go — An official, three-minute, introductory video from Google on getting started with Go’s newest fuzz testing features (or, if you prefer, a written tutorial). Elsewhere, Khaled Yakdan writes about improvements being made to fuzzing for Go 1.19 – a lot of work has gone into this.
Nooras Saba (Google) 


  
  
Making Code Faster — When someone with Tim’s experience talks about improving code performance, it never makes for a bad read. Here he shares a story of profiling some Go code. His approach is simple: Test, Benchmark, Refactor, Iterate.
Tim Bray 


  
  
Gophers - Opportunity is Knocking — We’re a premier software engineering firm looking for mid to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Golang Weekly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Loop Through an Array in JavaScript – JS Iterate Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-loop-through-an-array-in-javascript-js-iterate-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-loop-through-an-array-in-javascript-js-iterate-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T19:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An array is a single variable used to store elements of different datatypes so that they can be accessed through a single variable.  It is an ordered list of values, and each value is referred to as an element, which is specified by an index. Knowing that these single]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Capitalize First Letter – How to Uppercase the First Letter in a Word with JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-capitalize-first-letter-of-word/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-capitalize-first-letter-of-word/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T15:46:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're coding, there are many ways to capitalize the first letter of a word. You can use CSS as well as some JavaScript methods. In this article, I will show you one approach to achieve this. To capitalize the first letter of a word with JS, you need to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove Underline from a Link in CSS – HTML Style Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/remove-underline-from-link-in-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/remove-underline-from-link-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T15:41:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a web developer, you've probably wanted to get rid of the default underline that appears when you add a link to a page. Fortunately, just like other elements on a web page, you can style the anchor tags responsible for displaying a link. In this article, I will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mathematical Connect-the-Dots Reveals How Structure Emerges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=116133</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/new-proof-shows-when-structure-must-emerge-in-graphs-20220623/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T13:46:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new proof identifies precisely how large a mathematical graph must be before it contains a regular substructure.            
The post Mathematical Connect-the-Dots Reveals How Structure Emerges first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leila Sloman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Azure CosmosDB – Database Guide for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-beginners-guide-to-azure-cosmosdb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-beginners-guide-to-azure-cosmosdb/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T23:37:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will go through the basics of Azure Cosmos DB and understand the configuration options available with it.  We will cover resource management concepts, data model, APIs, and configuration options. 1. What is Azure Cosmos DB? Azure Cosmos DB is a document database service that enables]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhinav Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[%.2f in Python – What does it Mean?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/2f-in-python-what-does-it-mean/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/2f-in-python-what-does-it-mean/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T18:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, there are various methods for formatting data types.  The %f formatter is specifically used for formatting float values (numbers with decimals).  We can use the %f formatter to specify the number of decimal numbers to be returned when a floating point number is rounded up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Reset Origin – How to Reset a Local Branch to Remote Tracking Branch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-reset-origin-how-to-reset-a-local-branch-to-remote-tracking-branch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-reset-origin-how-to-reset-a-local-branch-to-remote-tracking-branch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T18:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a free and open-source version control system. It is the most popular version control system in use today. Git keeps track of the changes made to a project over time. This allows multiple developers to collaborate and work on the same project in parallel, no matter where they]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the DOM? The Document Object Model Explained in Plain English]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-the-dom-explained-in-plain-english/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-the-dom-explained-in-plain-english/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T17:54:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern web pages are dynamic. This means we need a suitable and convenient way to modify and manipulate a web document's structure.  This modification in an HTML document, for instance, usually takes the form of creating, adding, or removing elements in the document.  In this article, you'll learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>D.M. Oladele</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Array – How to Use Arrays in Your PHP Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-arrays-in-php/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-arrays-in-php/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T17:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An array is a special variable that we use to store or hold more than one value in a single variable without having to create more variables to store those values.  To create an array in PHP, we use the array function array( ). By default, an array of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoro Emmanuel Nzube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Design Patterns –Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-design-patterns-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-design-patterns-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T17:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article I'll explain what design patterns are and why they're useful.  We'll also go through some of the most popular design patterns out there and give examples for each of them. Let's go! Table of Contents  * What Are Design Patterns?  * Creational]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Spooky Quantum Phenomenon You’ve Never Heard Of]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=116105</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/the-spooky-quantum-phenomenon-youve-never-heard-of-20220622/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T14:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum computers may derive their power from the “magical” way that properties of particles change depending on the context.
            
The post The Spooky Quantum Phenomenon You’ve Never Heard Of first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katie McCormick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.15.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.15.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.15.1"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T06:05:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Favicon used as article image]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Recover a Deleted File in Git – Revert Changes After a Hard Reset]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-recover-a-deleted-file-in-git/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-recover-a-deleted-file-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T21:31:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a version control system that helps you keep track of the changes in a project's life cycle. It preserves the history of the project and allows you and your team members to coordinate effectively throughout.  There could be situations where you deleted a file and you want]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MVC in Computer Science – The MVC Model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-mvc-mean-in-computer-science/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-mvc-mean-in-computer-science/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T21:09:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MVC is an abbreviation that stands for Model, View, and Controller. This architectural pattern was created in the late 1970s for making desktop apps, but it is now widely used in web application development. In this article, I will dive deep into what MVC means alongside its 3 components, so]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Customize Bootstrap with Sass]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-customize-bootstrap-with-sass/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-customize-bootstrap-with-sass/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T20:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bootstrap is an awesome CSS framework that can help you create stylish and sleek websites.  Some developers and teams find that code written in Bootstrap is easier to maintain than regular CSS, so they prefer Bootstrap to vanilla CSS.  But if everyone used Bootstrap with its default styles,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vinod Mathew Sebastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Switch Statement – How to Use a Switch Case in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-switch-statement-how-to-use-a-switch-case-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-switch-statement-how-to-use-a-switch-case-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T17:39:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You use the switch statement in Java to execute a particular code block when a certain condition is met.  Here's what the syntax looks like: switch(expression) {   case 1:     // code block     break;   case 2:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up a Rasa Development Environment in Sagemaker Studiolab with VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/getting-started-with-rasa-with-studiolab-and-vscode/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/getting-started-with-rasa-with-studiolab-and-vscode/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T16:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, I was excited to dive into chatbot development with the open-source framework Rasa [https://rasa.com/]. With Rasa, you get a ton of flexibility, from designing the conversation to developing the NLU logic to deployment.  But the "Yay" soon transformed into banging my head against a brick wall. The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sijil Salim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is TypeScript? A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-typescript-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-typescript-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T15:55:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few weeks ago, I published an Intermediate TypeScript and React Handbook [/news/build-strongly-typed-polymorphic-components-with-react-and-typescript/]. It received many views and I got several emails. Most were “thank you” emails, but then there were others like: > “… I am new to programming, what is TypeScript?” And: > “Thanks for this free ebook,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmanuel Ohans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Consume REST APIs in React – a Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-consume-rest-apis-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-consume-rest-apis-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T15:35:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is a popular frontend library that developers use to create applications. And you will need to integrate APIs into your React application at some point if you want to build production-ready apps.  Every developer who wants to build modern, robust web applications with React must understand how to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Immunologist Fights Covid with Tweets and a Nasal Spray]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=116048</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/an-immunologist-fights-covid-with-tweets-and-a-nasal-spray-20220621/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T15:07:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Akiko Iwasaki, an immunologist who became a lifeline for the worried and the curious during the pandemic, thinks that nasal spray vaccines could be the next needed breakthrough in our fight against the coronavirus.            
The post An Immunologist Fights Covid with Tweets and a Nasal Spray first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yasemin Saplakoglu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate Your Life with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-your-life-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-your-life-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T14:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Think of the most boring task you’ve ever done. Chances are, you can automate it with Python! We just published a Python automation course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Frank Andrade created this course. Frank is a data scientist and experienced teacher. In this course you will learn how to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which Programming Language Should You Learn First?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/first-programming-language/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/first-programming-language/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T22:35:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a code newbie, one of the most intimidating yet fundamental decisions to make is deciding which programming language to learn first.  There is a wide variety of languages, frameworks, and libraries that you'll easily find if you Google around. You'll agree though that wherever there are a lot]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ophy Boamah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asynchronous JavaScript – Callbacks, Promises, and Async/Await Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/asynchronous-javascript-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/asynchronous-javascript-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T20:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've been learning JavaScript for a while now, then you've probably heard the term "asynchronous" before.  This is because JavaScript is an asynchronous language...but what does that really mean? In this article, I hope to show you that the concept is not as difficult as it sounds. Synchronous]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Njong Emy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Call, Apply, and Bind Functions in JavaScript – with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understand-call-apply-and-bind-in-javascript-with-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understand-call-apply-and-bind-in-javascript-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T18:25:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I am going to explain how to use call, apply, and bind in JavaScript with simple examples.  We will also implement an example that showcases how you can create your own map function with the apply function. Without further ado, let's get started. Table of Contents]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keyur Paralkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Absolute Value – Python abs Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-absolute-value-python-abs-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-absolute-value-python-abs-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T15:55:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn all about the abs() function in Python. You will learn what the abs() function does and why you may want to use it. You will also understand how to use abs() with the help of practical examples. Here is what we will cover:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Weekly #69 (#blogPost)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/web-weekly-69/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/web-weekly-69/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, hello party people!

Last week has been the day many poor souls waited for. Internet Explorer 11 left Microsoft's support rotation. No patches and security fixes anymore!
I haven't dealt with IE for ages, but I know folks that still had to tackle it occasionally. But does no support mean the outdated browser will just disappear? As Adrian puts it: "This doesn’t mean that the copy of IE11 on your client’s computer will suddenly uninstall itself." And this is true, but I think now's really the time to forget about it.
If you want to go down memory lane for a moment and see some "great" IE hacks, Pawel collected some nice ones to say goodbye.
And with this, today you'll learn about:
AbortController use cases
CSS terminology
font-display: optional
... and, as always, GitHub repositories…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend Reading — Gaslighting? With these prices?!]]></title>
        <id>62a52f6250eccb22d9896979</id>
        <link href="https://labnotes.org/weekend-reading-gaslighting-with-these-prices/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T00:45:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we DNS the weather, upgrade our workstation, find out who's making up all these AI images, and play dead like Sugar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Assaf Arkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.15.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.15.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.15.0"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T19:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Resolve relative URLs in item link and media
Added: Item thumbnail fallback to channel thumbnail
Chore: Dependency updates
Thank you: @cpwnd]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Get Current Date – Today's Date in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-get-current-date-todays-date-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-get-current-date-todays-date-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-17T15:45:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're developing web applications, you might need to include the current date on which a particular operation is performed.  For example, when submitting data via a form, you may want to include the date that data was created or when the form was submitted. In this article, we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Arrow – Symbol Unicode for Single and Double Arrows, Left and Right Arrows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-arrow-symbol-unicode-for-single-and-double-arrows-left-and-right-arrows/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-arrow-symbol-unicode-for-single-and-double-arrows-left-and-right-arrows/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-17T15:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are Unicodes? Unicodes are universal characters that represent different things. These could be symbols, characters, scripts, and many more forms of character combinations. Unicodes are adopted by many platforms (mobile and web) to make characters available everywhere. Why are Unicodes useful? Unicodes are useful because they provide a standard]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Visual Basic (.NET) – Full Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-visual-basic-net-full-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-visual-basic-net-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-17T14:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that Visual Basic is currently a more popular programming language than JavaScript? That is according to the TIOBE index [https://www.tiobe.com/tiobe-index/], which is one of the most respected indicators of the popularity of programming languages. Visual Basic is an object-oriented programming language developed by Microsoft. It makes it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing SIMD into Go?]]></title>
        <id>https://golangweekly.com/issues/416</id>
        <link href="https://golangweekly.com/issues/416"/>
        <updated>2022-06-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#​416 — June 17, 2022


Unsubscribe  |  Read on the Web



The Go Weekly Newsletter




  





  
  
Go 1.19 Beta 1 Released — This post on the golang-announce group just has the basics of how to download it, but these draft release notes go further into actual features (which are predominantly fixes and tweaks - don’t expect a big 1.18 style release, though the addition of an optional soft memory limit for the runtime is interesting).
The Go Team 


  
  
Language Proposal: Bring Direct SIMD Support into Go — Language proposals are always interesting to read, particularly when they provoke discussion; here, a simd library to take advantage of SIMD (Single Instruction, Multiple Data) CPU instructions is proposed and has been marked “active” by the core team for now.
Moritz Poldrack 


  
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Golang Weekly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Query Data in Google Spreadsheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/querying-like-an-sql-boss-in-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/querying-like-an-sql-boss-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T16:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I built a spreadsheet and wanted to display some of the data in a small table which would update based on the day of the week. After some digging, querying seemed the best option to pull this off. In this article, you'll learn several things about Google Sheets tables, functions,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Solve the Parking Lot Challenge in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/parking-lot-challenge-solved-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/parking-lot-challenge-solved-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T14:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you heard about the Parking Lot challenge? If not, let me explain briefly. The Parking Lot is challenge where you are asked to write a class that manages an imaginary parking lot.  In this tutorial we will do that in JavaScript. And to make it a bit more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mihail Gaberov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript forEach() – JS Array For Each Loop Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-foreach-js-array-for-each-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-foreach-js-array-for-each-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T14:52:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with arrays, there will be times when you need to loop or iterate through the array's values in order to either output or manipulate them.  These arrays can hold any datatype, including objects, numbers, strings, and many others. In this article, we'll look at how you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surfaces So Different Even a Fourth Dimension Can’t Make Them the Same]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=116009</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/special-surfaces-remain-distinct-in-four-dimensions-20220616/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T14:03:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For decades mathematicians have searched for a specific pair of surfaces that can’t be transformed into each other in four-dimensional space. Now they’ve found them.            
The post Surfaces So Different Even a Fourth Dimension Can’t Make Them the Same first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Hartnett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Popular Coding Challenge Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-most-popular-coding-challenge-websites/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-most-popular-coding-challenge-websites/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T22:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to improve your analytical skills, there's no better way to do that than solving problems. If you are a programmer, then this is something you should do for yourself. Programmers need to deal with all sorts of problems almost every day. Most importantly, solving problems in an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Life?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=115982</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/what-is-life-20220615/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T19:55:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Without a good definition of life, how do we look for it on alien planets? Steven Strogatz speaks with Robert Hazen, a mineralogist and astrobiologist, and Sheref Mansy, a chemist, to learn more.            
The post What Is Life? first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Strogatz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Help Translate freeCodeCamp into Your Native Language]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/help-translate-freecodecamp-language/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/help-translate-freecodecamp-language/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T16:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The freeCodeCamp community has been hard at work translating our 9,000+ tutorials into many world languages. Quality is everything. So instead of relying on machine translation, we are doing this entire process by hand. Dozens of native speakers are collaborating to make these free learning resources accessible to more people]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CRUD Operations – What is CRUD?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crud-operations-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crud-operations-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T16:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite being commonly pronounced /krʌd/, CRUD is not a word. It’s an abbreviation that stands for Create, Read, Update, and Delete or Destroy. In this article, I will show you what CRUD means, and what the individual terms mean and do. I will also show you how create, read, update,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wheel Made of ‘Odd Matter’ Spontaneously Rolls Uphill]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=115932</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/wheel-made-of-odd-matter-spontaneously-rolls-uphill-20220615/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T14:24:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Physicists have solved a key problem of robotic locomotion by revising the usual rules of interaction between simple component parts.            
The post Wheel Made of ‘Odd Matter’ Spontaneously Rolls Uphill first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Brubaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Text Classification with TensorFlow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/text-classification-tensorflow/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/text-classification-tensorflow/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T14:01:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Text classification algorithms are used in a lot of different software systems to help process text data. For example, when you get an email, the email software uses a text classification algorithm to decide whether to put it in your inbox or in your spam folder. It's also how discussion]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Sort Array – How to Reverse an Array in Ascending or Descending Order with Arrays.sort()]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-sort-array-how-to-reverse-an-array-in-ascending-or-descending-order-with-arrays-sort-2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-sort-array-how-to-reverse-an-array-in-ascending-or-descending-order-with-arrays-sort-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T21:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Java, you use arrays to store a collection of variables (with the same data type) in a single variable.  In many cases, the values stored in an array appear in a random order. Using the  Arrays class in Java, you have access to various methods you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve Cloud-Native System Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-cloud-native-system-performance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-cloud-native-system-performance/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T20:14:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web applications are built to provide various online services to end-users. Developing and hosting these services involves hard work and talent. And it all begins with an idea. But imagine, after putting in all that hard work, users cringe about the performance of the system – “It's too slow...”, “I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sumeet Ninawe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debouncing in React – How to Delay a JS Function]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/debouncing-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/debouncing-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:42:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are some heavy tasks in software development. Take calling an API, for example. Suppose we have an API that searches a list of users, and we can't afford to fire it too often. We want to search only when we have typed the whole search query.  Well, debouncing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nishant Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Link CSS to HTML – Stylesheet File Linking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-link-css-to-html/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-link-css-to-html/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:22:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML is the markup language that helps you define the structure of a web page. CSS is the stylesheet language you use to make the structure presentable and nicely laid out. To make the stylings you implement with CSS reflect in the CSS, you have to find a way to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Brain Has a ‘Low-Power Mode’ That Blunts Our Senses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=115884</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/the-brain-has-a-low-power-mode-that-blunts-our-senses-20220614/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T14:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neuroscientists uncovered an energy-saving mode in vision-system neurons that works at the cost of being able to see fine-grained details.            
The post The Brain Has a ‘Low-Power Mode’ That Blunts Our Senses first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison Whitten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Computer Scientist Who Parlays Failures Into Breakthroughs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=115826</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/the-computer-scientist-who-parlays-failures-into-breakthroughs-20220613/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T14:31:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Spielman solves important problems by thinking hard — about other questions.             
The post The Computer Scientist Who Parlays Failures Into Breakthroughs first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mordechai Rorvig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If Statement in C – How to use If-Else Statements in the C Programming Language]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/if-statement-in-c-how-to-use-if-else-statements-in-the-c-programming-language/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/if-statement-in-c-how-to-use-if-else-statements-in-the-c-programming-language/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T13:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the C programming language, you have the ability to control the flow of a program. In particular, the program is able to make decisions on what it should do next. And those decisions are based on the state of certain pre-defined conditions you set. The program will decide what]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Weekly #68 (#blogPost)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/web-weekly-68/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/web-weekly-68/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-12T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buna ziua, friends!

In preparation for my new talk "Back to boring" I looked at the Open UI project whose goal is to standardize more UI components.
The idea is simple. If there are components that are included and reinvented in every design system out there, shouldn't these components become HTML elements? Big yes from my side!
And there are good things in the making:
selectmenu will enable us to build styleable select controls finally.
popup will help to show and hide elements on click or keyboard navigation.
focusgroup will make custom controls more accessible.
I can't wait until I can build accessible components like the one below without JavaScript.
The project's still in the early stages, but I'm 100% convinced we need more high-level HTML components. The web evolved, and if 95% of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend Reading — 🐝 If bees are fish …]]></title>
        <id>62a0c65050eccb22d9895eb4</id>
        <link href="https://labnotes.org/weekend-reading-if-bees-are-fish/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-12T00:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we get schooled by ML, find new uses for iDevices, go fishing for bees, and can you get these dishes unstuck?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Assaf Arkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["fetch" supports a "keepAlive" option to make it outlive page navigations (#tilPost)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/today-i-learned/fetch-supports-a-keepalive-option-to-make-it-outlive-page-navigations/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/today-i-learned/fetch-supports-a-keepalive-option-to-make-it-outlive-page-navigations/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-11T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This site uses Umami as a self-hosted and privacy-first analytics tool. An item in Umami's changelog caught my eye – "Update tracker/index.js: SendBeacon() to Fetch API".
sendBeacon is a JavaScript method to send requests to an analytics server. These requests are supposed to be async, not be canceled and outlive the current navigation. But apparently, sendBeacon is sometimes blocked by ad blockers.
That's not a big deal, though, because today I learned I can drop sendBeacon from my memory entirely and use the fetch method with a keepalive option. 👇
fetch(`${root}/api/collect`, {
  method: 'POST',
  body: data,
  // note the `keepalive` option
  keepalive: true,
});

fetch with a keepalive option has the same characteristics as sendBeacon and acts as its replacement. This is good to know!
Don't confuse the keepalive fetch attribute with the Keep-Alive HTTP header.


          
          
            Reply to Stefan]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Variable in Python – Non-Local Python Variables]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/global-variable-in-python-non-local-python-variables/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/global-variable-in-python-non-local-python-variables/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T21:21:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python and most programming languages, variables declared outside a function are known as global variables. You can access such variables inside and outside of a function, as they have global scope.  Here's an example of a global variable: x = 10  def showX():]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn PHP Syntax, Comments, Variables and Data Types – with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/php-syntax-comments-variables-data-types-with-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/php-syntax-comments-variables-data-types-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T20:18:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to today's tutorial, everyone. In my last article [/news/how-to-get-started-with-php/], I walked you through what PHP is and how to get it set up along with XAMPP.  And today, we'll review those introductory PHP concepts and then dive into the language a bit more in depth. We'll look at]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoro Emmanuel Nzube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Front End Developer – Front End Web Dev Skills]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-frontend-developer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-frontend-developer/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T20:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the highest-paid professionals in the world are front-end developers. They use their knowledge and talents to design appealing and user-friendly websites. Front-end developers do not need a degree or a school certificate to work. Rather, they must understand the fundamentals of front-end development, programming languages, and front-end development]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Statistics for Beginners – Top Stats Concepts to Know Before Getting into Data Science]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/top-statistics-concepts-to-know-before-getting-into-data-science/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/top-statistics-concepts-to-know-before-getting-into-data-science/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T16:33:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You've probably heard that statistics is the gateway to data science and that the data science map starts with stats. Perhaps you've also heard from others that you have to learn statistics before learning data science.  But then you ponder, "Since I'm not from a technical background like science, technology,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ibrahim Abayomi Ogunbiyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Screenshot on Windows – Take a Screen Shot on PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-screenshot-on-windows-take-a-screen-shot-on-pc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-screenshot-on-windows-take-a-screen-shot-on-pc/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T15:01:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just like you can take screenshots on your phone, you can also do the same on your Windows computer. Whether you want to take a screenshot of a particular part of your screen or you want to take a screenshot of the whole screen, there are tools and keyboard combinations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Extract Pages from a PDF and Render Them with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/extract-pdf-pages-render-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/extract-pdf-pages-render-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T03:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PDF stands for portable document format. PDFs were designed by Adobe in the 90s for Windows. They are self-contained documents with support for nearly all major operating systems.  But sometimes you'll need to modify a PDF to suit your needs and not just view it. Unfortunately, the available software]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hrishikesh Pathak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The star of the Go]]></title>
        <id>https://golangweekly.com/issues/415</id>
        <link href="https://golangweekly.com/issues/415"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#​415 — June 10, 2022


Unsubscribe  |  Read on the Web



The Go Weekly Newsletter




  





Go has passed 100,000 stars on GitHub. There was no obvious top feature this week, so what better way to celebrate than to mark the (arguably quite arbitrary) milestone of Go passing into the six figure GitHub stars club? I mean, it's twice as many as Ruby on Rails has, and GitHub was built with that.. :-)





  
  
Data Race Patterns in Go — Uber's engineers analyzed over 1,100 data races and found that it’s much easier than you might think to introduce them in Go "due to certain language design choices." This post breaks down seven of the most common reasons – your code probably engages in one of them too.
Chabbi and Ramanathan (Uber) 


  
  
Ebiten, the 2D Game Library for Go, Becomes Ebite…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Golang Weekly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Higher Order Functions in JavaScript – Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/higher-order-functions-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/higher-order-functions-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T19:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, functions are treated as first-class citizens. We can treat functions as values and assign them to another variable, pass them as arguments to another function, or even return them from another function. This ability of functions to act as first-class functions is what powers higher order functions in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soham De Roy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In-Demand Tech Skills for 2022 –Lessons Learned from Candidate Data from 191 Countries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/in-demand-tech-skills-devskiller-report/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/in-demand-tech-skills-devskiller-report/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T19:47:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A popular Chinese proverb says: “The best time to plant a tree was 20 years ago. The second best time is now.”  The same applies to acquiring new tech skills. No matter if you’re a junior developer or a seasoned software engineer, there is always something you can work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakub Kubrynski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No-Code Tools to Use for Your Next Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/no-code-tools-for-building-your-next-project/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/no-code-tools-for-building-your-next-project/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T19:38:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have recently started being active in a couple of online maker communities, and I've met a lot of talented folks who are building amazing products.  One thing that has stood out to me while engaging with these makers is that many of them are not developers – in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shayan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Type the Vertical Line | Bar Character on a Keyboard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-type-the-vertical-line-bar-character-on-a-keyboard/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-type-the-vertical-line-bar-character-on-a-keyboard/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T16:06:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We use the vertical line character, |, in various scenarios and contexts. You'll use it in mathematics and programming, in Linux, and in computer science fields to represent different things. Programmers also call this character the pipe symbol. What is the Pipe Character Used For? In Mathematics, the double pipe]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Set – How to Create a Set in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-set-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-set-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sets are defined as a collection of objects. They are an important concept in math and programming.  Programming languages provide different ways to group objects. Lists, dictionaries, and arrays are some examples of grouping objects.  Python has its own methods of creating a collection of objects. In Python,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded Rust Programming on Raspberry Pi Zero W]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/embedded-rust-programming-on-raspberry-pi-zero-w/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/embedded-rust-programming-on-raspberry-pi-zero-w/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:37:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded programming in Rust requires a whole new knowledge base. Using a Raspberry Pi Zero W, you can quickly get up and running with embedded Rust. Starting with an embedded "Hello World" equivalent, and advancing to a text-to-morse-code translator, this article will walk you through the process.  * How]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaun Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use fnm – Fast Node Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fnm-fast-node-manager/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fnm-fast-node-manager/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've been working with Node for a while, you will most likely discover that your projects – or one you're working on – are written for an older version of Node. That means they won't work as expected with the latest version.  In that case, a Node version]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Biswas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Horizontal vs. Vertical Scaling – How to Scale a Database]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/horizontal-vs-vertical-scaling-in-database/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/horizontal-vs-vertical-scaling-in-database/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:26:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data Scalability Data scalability refers to the ability of a database to manipulate changing demands by adding and removing data. In this way, the database grows at the same pace as the software.  Via scaling, the database can expand or contract the capacity of the system's resources to support]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Iroegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Full Stack Amazon Clone with Flutter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-amazon-clone-with-flutter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-amazon-clone-with-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T14:11:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people complain about Amazon's UI but most people realize how complex Amazon's website truly is. If you want to improve your skills as a full stack developer, creating an Amazon clone will give you practice in many different areas. We just published a 12-hour course that will teach you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomers Reimagine the Making of the Planets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=115783</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/how-are-planets-made-new-theories-are-taking-shape-20220609/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T13:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Observations of faraway planets have forced a near-total rewrite of the story of how our solar system came to be.
            
The post Astronomers Reimagine the Making of the Planets first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca Boyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inline Style in HTML – CSS Inline Styles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/inline-style-in-html/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/inline-style-in-html/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T21:24:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) is a markup language that determines how your web pages will appear. It manages the colors, fonts, and layouts of your website elements, as well as allowing you to add effects or animations to your pages. We can style an HTML file/page in three ways: external]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Error 502 Bad Gateway Meaning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/error-502-bad-gateway-meaning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/error-502-bad-gateway-meaning/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T20:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you visit a website and you get a “502 Bad Gateway” error, it means there’s an issue with the servers powering the website. On many occasions, this error is an issue with the website itself, so on your end, there’s nothing you can do to solve it. But the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python enumerate() – What is the Enumerate Function in Python?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-enumerate-what-is-the-enumerate-function-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-enumerate-what-is-the-enumerate-function-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T19:56:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The enumerate() function in Python takes in a data collection as a parameter and returns an enumerate object.  The enumerate object is returned in a key-value pair format. The key is the corresponding index of each item and the value is the items.  In this article, we'll see]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove a Directory in Linux – Delete a Folder Command]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-a-directory-in-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-a-directory-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T17:11:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're using a user interface, you can right-click on a directory and select "Delete" or "Move to Bin". But how do you do this on the terminal? I'll explain that in this article. How to Remove a Directory in Linux There are two ways to remove directories in Linux:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Any UI in Flutter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-any-ui-in-flutter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-any-ui-in-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T15:22:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to convert any user interface image, piece, or screen into Flutter [https://flutter.dev] code. This is not a tutorial on building an app. It is rather a guide that will help you implement any UI you come across into an app you already have.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Obumuneme Nwabude</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Speech Recognition in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/speech-recognition-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/speech-recognition-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T14:10:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speech recognition allows software to recognize speech within audio and convert it into text. There are many interesting use-cases for speech recognition and it is easier than you may think to add it your own applications. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Achieve ‘Absurdly Fast’ Algorithm for Network Flow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=115736</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/researchers-achieve-absurdly-fast-algorithm-for-network-flow-20220608/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T14:04:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computer scientists can now solve a decades-old problem in practically the time it takes to write it down.            
The post Researchers Achieve ‘Absurdly Fast’ Algorithm for Network Flow first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erica Klarreich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Components – How to Create a Search, Filter, and Pagination Component in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-react-components/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-react-components/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T23:37:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wrote the article "How to Search and Filter Components in React" exactly one year ago. > If you're building a React app, you want your users to be able to search & get exact results. And if you're getting data from an API, they need to be able to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spruce Emmanuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add JWT Authentication in FastAPI – A Practical Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-jwt-authentication-in-fastapi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-jwt-authentication-in-fastapi/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T23:28:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FastAPI [https://fastapi.tiangolo.com/] is a modern, fast, battle tested and light-weight web development framework written in Python. Other popular options in the space are Django [https://www.djangoproject.com/], Flask [https://flask.palletsprojects.com/en/2.1.x/]and Bottle [https://bottlepy.org/docs/dev/]. And since it's new, FastAPI comes with both advantages and disadvantages. On the positive side, FastAPI implements all the modern standards,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdullah Adeel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello World in Java – Example Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hello-world-in-java-example-program/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hello-world-in-java-example-program/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T17:13:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're learning a new programming language, you'll often see the first program called a "Hello World" program. It's used in most cases as a simple program for beginners.  I will assume that you're either reading this article as a beginner to the Java programming language or you're here]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change Font with HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-change-font-with-html/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-change-font-with-html/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T16:41:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in the days of HTML4, there was a  tag you could use to change the font size, font family, and the color of a text. But with HTML5, the  tag has been deprecated. So if you want to change anything related to the font, you have to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage PostgreSQL Databases from the Command Line with psql]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manage-postgresql-with-psql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manage-postgresql-with-psql/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T15:29:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now is a great time to learn relational databases and SQL. From web development to data science, they are used everywhere.  In the Stack Overflow 2021 Survey [https://insights.stackoverflow.com/survey/2021#most-popular-technologies-database-prof] , 4 out of the top 5 database technologies used by professional developers were relational database management systems. PostgreSQL is an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gerard Hynes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reshuffled Rivers Bolster the Amazon’s Hyper-Biodiversity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=115635</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/reshuffled-rivers-bolster-the-amazons-hyper-biodiversity-20220607/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T13:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The lush biodiversity of the Amazon may be due in part to the dynamics of branching rivers, which serve as invisible fences that continuously barricade and merge bird populations.            
The post Reshuffled Rivers Bolster the Amazon’s Hyper-Biodiversity first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yasemin Saplakoglu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Prepare for Technical Interviews – Problem-Solving Tips + Mindset Tricks to Get You Ready]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/problem-solving-and-technical-interview-prep/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/problem-solving-and-technical-interview-prep/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T22:50:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we're going to talk a bit about technical interviews. I'll share a few tips that, based on my experience, might help you go through these interviews successfully. I originally wrote this article more than a year ago, before getting my first job offer as a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Foundational Mathematics on freeCodeCamp – Interactive Math Courses Open Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-foundational-math-curriculum/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-foundational-math-curriculum/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T21:58:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to use Python to solve math problems? Then freeCodeCamp's new Foundational Math course will guide you through the essential math you need to know to prepare you for the Data Science curriculum.  You will get a math refresher with a twist. Instead of using a pencil]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Pratowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Interview Questions – Interview Prep with Answers and Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-interview-questions-and-answers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-interview-questions-and-answers/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T21:55:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is a JavaScript library for creating user interfaces. It's used in over 30,000 live websites and has over 70,000 GitHub stars.  According to the 2021 Stack Overflow developer survey [https://insights.stackoverflow.com/survey/2021#section-most-popular-technologies-web-frameworks] , React has surpassed jQuery as the most popular web framework, and holds approximately 40.14% of the market]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does a Data Analyst Do? Data Analyst Job Description]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-a-data-analyst-do-data-analyst-job-description/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-a-data-analyst-do-data-analyst-job-description/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T20:44:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We live in a digital world, and with each passing day, we create 2.5 quintillion  bytes of data. That amount of data is generated by activities like browsing the web, using social media sites and streaming platforms, and communicating via instant messaging applications with friends and family. These are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does K8s Mean? How to Set Up Kubernetes and Manage Clusters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-k8s-mean-kubernetes-setup-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-k8s-mean-kubernetes-setup-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might've seen the term k8s in different sources, and wondered what it means. Well, it means Kubernetes. The abbreviation consists of:  * "k" which is the first letter of Kubernetes,  * "8" which is the number of letters between the first and the last in the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sigl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Checkout – How to Checkout a File from Another Branch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-checkout-file-from-another-branch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-checkout-file-from-another-branch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:36:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While you're working on a repository in Git, you might need to checkout a specific file from another branch. Luckily, Git offers many possible ways to do this task quickly. One of the easiest solutions is to use the git checkout command with the specified file as an argument. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Mouskhelichvili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux cp Command – How to Copy Files in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-linux-cp-command-how-to-copy-files-in-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-linux-cp-command-how-to-copy-files-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a couple different ways to copy and paste content when you're working on your computer. If you spend more time in the user interface of your device, you'll probably use your mouse to do this. You can copy files by right-clicking on the file and selecting "Copy", then]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Insert a Checkbox in Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-insert-a-checkbox-in-excel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-insert-a-checkbox-in-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T15:53:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Excel is a dynamic data analysis tool you can use to do virtually anything. From charting, graphing, and financial analysis to interactive forms and to-do lists, it's got you covered. If you want to use Excel to make a To-do list, an interactive form, or a printable form, then]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crow's Foot Notation – Relationship Symbols And How to Read Diagrams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crows-foot-notation-relationship-symbols-and-how-to-read-diagrams/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crows-foot-notation-relationship-symbols-and-how-to-read-diagrams/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T15:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Entity relationship diagrams (ERD) help us understand the connection between various "entities" that make up a system.  In software development, ERDs are mostly used in database design. This lets us create graphical representations of the entities that make up systems such as a database (you will understand this better]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Algorithms – with JavaScript Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-algorithms-with-javascript-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-algorithms-with-javascript-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T14:40:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we're going to take a look at algorithms, a key topic when it comes to computer science and software development. Algorithm is a fancy, sometimes intimidating, and often misunderstood word. It sounds like something really hard and complex, but actually it's nothing more than a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graduate Student’s Side Project Proves Prime Number Conjecture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=115637</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/graduate-students-side-project-proves-prime-number-conjecture-20220606/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T13:36:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jared Duker Lichtman, 26, has proved a longstanding conjecture relating prime numbers to a broad class of “primitive” sets. To his adviser, it came as a “complete shock.”             
The post Graduate Student’s Side Project Proves Prime Number Conjecture first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordana Cepelewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git List Remote Branches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-list-remote-branches/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-list-remote-branches/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T23:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are 4 different Git commands you can enter into your command line to list all of the remote branches of a repo. I will show you command line code examples of each of these. For all of these examples, I will use freeCodeCamp's open source repository [https://github.com/freeCodeCamp/freeCodeCamp/]. Command #1:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend Reading — What's Latin for Waffle House?]]></title>
        <id>6292ba8418f2762794c295b2</id>
        <link href="https://labnotes.org/weekend-reading-whats-latin-for-waffle-house/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T16:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we learn the DALLE language, discover infinite disk space, and bring flexbox to 1986.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Assaf Arkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>