<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://daorren.github.io/osmofeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-01-17T01:27:01.148Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://daorren.github.io/osmofeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://daorren.github.io/osmofeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Format Output You Send to the Console]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/formatting-output-to-the-console/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/formatting-output-to-the-console/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T21:46:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have been a programmer for a while, then you have likely used a  console.log to display data.  You may want to see the value of data while your program is running, or you may be trying to troubleshoot a problem.  Sometimes the data displayed in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Hide Your API Keys in an Android Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hide-your-api-keys-in-android/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hide-your-api-keys-in-android/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T21:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's say that you are using a version control system and your project uses services that require API keys. Everything is all good when they're on your local machine, but you don’t want to share these API keys with the world. So how can you still preserve your API keys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Ben Rachel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Cloud Computing? Explained for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-cloud-computing-beginners-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-cloud-computing-beginners-guide/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T19:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may not always be aware of it, but you're enjoying the many fruits of the cloud just about every hour of every day. Many of the joys (and horrors) of modern life would be impossible without it.  Before we talk about what it does and where it's taking]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run Your Own Decentralized Authentication Service Using AuthN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-run-your-own-decentralized-authentication-service-using-authn/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-run-your-own-decentralized-authentication-service-using-authn/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T18:32:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The old authentication systems from monolithic applications don't work well in modern applications. When you build a web-application, you need a way to handle user authentication (the ability for a user to log in to your web-application). Traditionally, web-applications were built as monoliths and authentication systems were installed via a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Brown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Grid to List Toggle using CSS Grid and JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/grid-to-list-toggle-using-css-grid/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/grid-to-list-toggle-using-css-grid/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T17:13:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will show you how to create a toggle to display items in a grid from a list. This will be using basic JavaScript skills with no external code or libraries. We will be using CSS Grid. What We Will Be Creating How to Create Our Starter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend Reading — 👋 Shut the front door]]></title>
        <id>63bb549ad539c067d0635ec5</id>
        <link href="https://labnotes.org/weekend-reading-shut-the-front-door/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-15T01:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we compare JS component libraries, steer clear of YAML, impressed by text-to-draw tech, and dream of a giant dog bed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Assaf Arkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Real-time Chat App with ReactJS and Firebase]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/building-a-real-time-chat-app-with-reactjs-and-firebase/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/building-a-real-time-chat-app-with-reactjs-and-firebase/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T22:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'm going to show you how to build a real-time chat app using React.js and Firebase.  In the app, we will allow the user to log in with their Google account using Firebase's Google sign-in Authentication. We will also store and retrieve all the chatroom messages]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timonwa Akintokun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Search Functionality to a Ruby on Rails Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-search-to-ruby-on-rails-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-search-to-ruby-on-rails-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T18:22:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nowadays, most web applications have a search feature. Users can use the search feature in order to navigate websites more easily. Implementing a search feature in Ruby on Rails is very easy. By using only a few lines of code you can set it up. This tutorial assumes that you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sampurna Chapagain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Rename a Column in Pandas – Python Pandas Dataframe Renaming Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-rename-a-column-in-pandas/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-rename-a-column-in-pandas/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T18:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Pandas Dataframe is a 2-dimensional data structure that displays data in tables with rows and columns.  In this article, you'll learn how to rename columns in a Pandas Dataframe by using:   * The rename() function.  * A List.  * The set_axis() function. How to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coalesce SQL – Example PostgreSQL and SQL Server Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/coalesce-sql-example-postgresql-and-sql-server-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/coalesce-sql-example-postgresql-and-sql-server-functions/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T18:14:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In SQL, the COALESCE() function returns the first non-null value in an entry. It evaluates the values of the entries one by one, ignores the null values, then returns the first value that is not null. It works in PostgreSQL, SQL server, and MySQL. In this article, I will show]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C# Coding Best Practices – Coding Conventions with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/coding-best-practices-in-c-sharp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/coding-best-practices-in-c-sharp/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T16:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coding conventions ensure that your code is consistent, readable, understandable, and maintainable.  When it comes to writing clean and quality code, there are conventions developers should follow to make this possible.  There are a few things you should keep in mind while writing your code. In this article,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[File Permissions in Linux – How to Use the chown and chgrp Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/file-permissions-in-linux-how-to-use-the-chown-chgrp-command-s/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/file-permissions-in-linux-how-to-use-the-chown-chgrp-command-s/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T16:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to large organizations, Users and Groups in Linux play an important role in helping keep systems secure and properly functioning.  There can be different levels of users in an organization with different roles and permissions. And you'll need a good understanding Linux permissions to manage and/or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Block Mirror]]></title>
        <id>https://golangweekly.com/issues/443</id>
        <link href="https://golangweekly.com/issues/443"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#​443 — January 13, 2023


Unsub  |  Web Version



The Go Weekly Newsletter





  
  
What’s New in Go 1.20: Language Changes — The first in a (scheduled) three-part series, this post discusses tweaks to interfaces, generics, unsafe, as well as a new slice to array conversion technique.
Carl M. Johnson 


In related news, Go 1.20 release candidate 3 has just been released – its main fix is for this macOS bug so Mac users are particularly encouraged to test against it. Go 1.19.5 and 1.18.10 have also been released this week.





  
  
Embedding Our New React UI in Go — Flipt serves its web application from a single Go binary, embedding the static assets therein. Go 1.16’s native embedding set them on a journey that led to React and it works pretty well - no Next.js needed.
George MacRori…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Golang Weekly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is SQL? Database Definition for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-sql-database-definition-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-sql-database-definition-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T18:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data is a powerful tool that drives everything you see and interact with on the internet. It facilitates research and powers today's technology. It is the driving force behind today's artificial intelligence and robotics. And so much more. Previously, these data were stored on paper, in physical files within cabinets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Grid-to-List Layout Toggle using Flexbox and JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flexbox-grid-to-list-toggle-using-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flexbox-grid-to-list-toggle-using-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T17:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will show you how to create a toggle to display items in a grid from a list. We'll do this using basic JavaScript skills with no external code or libraries. We will be using Flexbox to help us accomplish this. What We Will Be Creating Here's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software System Design for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/software-system-design-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/software-system-design-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T15:47:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building large-scale distributed systems like Google, Facebook, Amazon, and Twitter requires an in-depth understanding of computer science principles. This allows systems to handle millions of users concurrently despite hardware failures. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to design software systems. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Probability and Number Theory Collide — in a Moment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=122102</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/in-a-moment-mathematicians-merge-probability-and-number-theory-20230112/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T15:37:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mathematicians are taking ideas developed to study random numbers and applying them to a broad range of categories.            
The post Probability and Number Theory Collide — in a Moment first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leila Sloman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matplotlib Figure Size – How to Change Plot Size in Python with plt.figsize()]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/matplotlib-figure-size-change-plot-size-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/matplotlib-figure-size-change-plot-size-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T15:29:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When creating plots using Matplotlib, you get a default figure size of 6.4 for the width and 4.8 for the height (in inches). In this article, you'll learn how to change the plot size using the following:   * The figsize() attribute.   * The set_figwidth() method.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[var, let, and const in JavaScript – the Differences Between These Keywords Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/differences-between-var-let-const-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/differences-between-var-let-const-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T22:48:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, you can declare variables with the var, let, and const keywords. But what are the differences between them? That's what I'll explain in this tutorial. I have a video version of this topic [https://youtu.be/Gd_JG3e1g4A] you can check out as well. 😇 If you're just starting out using JavaScript,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Accessibility – Common ARIA Mistakes to Avoid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-accessibility-common-aria-mistakes-to-avoid/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-accessibility-common-aria-mistakes-to-avoid/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T21:58:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible Rich Internet Applications – or ARIA – is a set of attributes and roles defined by the Web Accessibility Initiative [https://www.w3.org/WAI/]. These make the web more accessible to people with disabilities.  ARIA is extremely important for building accessible web applications. But it's very easy to misuse ARIA and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilknur Eren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS by Building the Google Logo in Pure CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-google-logo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-google-logo/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T19:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best ways to learn CSS is by creating something useful while you learn. I will show you how to use the following CSS items by creating the Google logo:  * position relative and absolute  * pseudo classes ::before and ::after  * positioning an element]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React Dev Tools – With Example Code and Videos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-dev-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-dev-tools/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T18:18:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working on a React project, one of the easiest ways to debug your code is using the React Dev Tools. React Dev Tools is an extension created by the React team. It enables developers to debug their code inside their Developer Tools. Once you add the extension, you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aman Kalra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accounting Number Format in Excel – How to Apply it to Selected Cells]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/accounting-number-format-in-excel-how-to-apply-it-to-selected-cells/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/accounting-number-format-in-excel-how-to-apply-it-to-selected-cells/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T18:11:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I will show you how to format cells in Microsoft Excel. We'll be looking particularly at the Accounting format for cells with numbers.  At the end of the article I'll give you two bonuses: a short video walkthrough of the methods we go over, as well]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developing Games Using Unreal Engine 5]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/developing-games-using-unreal-engine-5/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/developing-games-using-unreal-engine-5/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T15:27:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unreal Engine 5 is a powerful game engine that has been used to create some of the most popular and critically acclaimed games in recent years.  We just published an 11-hour Unreal Engine course for beginners on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Sourav created this coruse. He has 7 years]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starfish Whisperer Develops a Physical Language of Life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=122062</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/starfish-whisperer-develops-a-physical-language-of-life-20230111/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T15:21:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nikta Fakhri is adapting and extending concepts from physics to describe how tiny biological components give rise to living organisms.             
The post Starfish Whisperer Develops a Physical Language of Life first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Charlie Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS by Building the Git Logo in Pure CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-git-logo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-git-logo/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T18:54:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best ways to learn CSS is by creating something useful while you learn. I will show you how to use the following CSS items by creating the Git logo:  * Transform to rotate an image  * position relative and absolute  * pseudo classes ::before]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL CONVERT – The DATE to String or DATETIME Function]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-convert-the-date-to-string-or-datetime-function-2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-convert-the-date-to-string-or-datetime-function-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T18:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with SQL, you'll need to learn how to format dates properly. This is because dates are an important aspect of any SQL and other software-related activities. You need to be able to work with dates to add timestamps to entries and keep track of when things happen,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Joins – LEFT Join, RIGHT Join, and INNER Join Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-sql-joins/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-sql-joins/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T18:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SQL is a programming language we use to interact with relational databases. SQL databases contain tables, which contain rows of data. These tables usually contain similar or related data. In an office management web application database, you would have tables for  employees, their departments, their managers, the projects they]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zubair Idris Aweda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Performance – How to Improve Page Speed with async and defer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-performance-async-defer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-performance-async-defer/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T18:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In web programming, JavaScript brings interactiveness and dynamic behaviour to your web pages. While HTML and CSS take care of the structure and aesthetics of the pages, they will be merely usable without JavaScript doing its job in the background. You can include JavaScript code in the HTML file in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Projects for Beginners in 2023 – Fun Ideas with Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-projects-for-beginners-easy-ideas-with-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-projects-for-beginners-easy-ideas-with-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T17:53:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You're ready to start making simple projects with React, but you don't know what to make. Where should you start? I have created seven unique and fun React projects for you to make, all of which will teach you essential React concepts that you need to know in 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Digital Privacy? A Beginner's Guide to Protecting Your Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/beginners-guide-to-digital-privacy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/beginners-guide-to-digital-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T17:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For all the many benefits we enjoy from technology – and particularly the technologies that make up the public internet – there are plenty of costs, too.  Figuring out how you want to balance the benefits against the costs can take some careful thinking. Here's a concise and effective]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ants Live 10 Times Longer by Altering Their Insulin Responses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=122007</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/ants-live-10-times-longer-by-altering-their-insulin-responses-20230110/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T16:46:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Queen ants live far longer than genetically identical workers. Researchers are learning what their longevity secrets could mean for aging in other species.            
The post Ants Live 10 Times Longer by Altering Their Insulin Responses first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Viviane Callier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Props in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/props-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/props-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T16:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're first learning React, props are often one of the most difficult topics to understand – especially when it comes to passing props across components. And when you need similar props in more than one component, things can get really tricky. In this guide, we will start by understanding]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tooba Jamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS by Building the Nextflix Logo in Pure CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-nextflix-logo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-nextflix-logo/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T01:37:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best ways to learn CSS is by creating something useful while you learn. I will show you how to use the following CSS concepts by creating the Netflix logo:  * border-left and border-right  * pseudo class ::before  * box-shadow  * transform: skewX What]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Better Web Developer in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-better-web-developer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-better-web-developer/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T23:05:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web development is a highly in-demand and popular skill these days. So if you’re at a crossroads in your life and thinking about becoming a web developer – or just want to further improve your skills – read on. To be a great web developer, you must learn many skills]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shahan Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Review of CS50 – Harvard's Introduction to Computer Science Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cs50-course-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cs50-course-review/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T22:20:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you considering taking the CS50 [/news/harvard-cs50/] Introduction to Computer Science course, but wondering if it's the right fit for you?  As someone who doesn’t have a computer science degree and was looking to learn the fundamentals of the field, I was in the same boat. That's why I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoebe Voong-Fadel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Setup React and Tailwind CSS with Vite in a Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-tailwindcss-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-tailwindcss-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T18:49:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tailwind CSS is a popular CSS framework, and React is one of the most popular JavaScript libraries. And Tailwind CSS and React are a great combo to use if you're building a frontend project. In this article, you will learn how to setup your coding environment with Vite, install React]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Segun Ajibola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Synthetic Identity Theft and How to Protect Yourself]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/synthetic-identity-theft/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/synthetic-identity-theft/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T18:42:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s digital age, cybercriminals have no shortage of methods to steal people's identities and sensitive data. One such method is synthetic identity theft, which is becoming one of the most dangerous and common forms.  In fact, according to a figures published by Federal Reserve Bank of Boston [https://www.bostonfed.org/news-and-events/news/2022/08/synthetic-identity-fraud-is-not-a-victimless-crime-costs-billions-damages-lives.aspx]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dmitry Dragilev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS by Building the React Logo in Pure CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-react-logo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-react-logo/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T18:21:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best ways to learn CSS is by creating something useful while you learn. I will show you how to use the following CSS concepts by creating the React logo:  * position: absolute  * vw (view width)  * transform: rotate()  * animation using keyframes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Email Verification in a Flask App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/setup-email-verification-in-flask-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/setup-email-verification-in-flask-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T17:56:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Email verification is a crucial aspect of creating a new user account or signing up for a service. It helps confirm that the email address provided is valid and belongs to the intended user. In this article, we will explore the process of handling email verification in Flask. The topic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Google Like a Pro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-google-like-a-pro/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-google-like-a-pro/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T15:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you tired of sifting through pages of irrelevant search results? Do you want to become more efficient at finding the information you need on the web? If so, this course is for you. We just published a video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Delete a File in Python – And Remove a Directory, Too]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-delete-a-file-in-python-and-remove-a-directory-too/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-delete-a-file-in-python-and-remove-a-directory-too/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T15:24:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python offers many standard utility modules which enable several functions in the applications we build. In this article, we'll learn about the modules for deleting files and directories. One of the most popular modules exposed in Python is the os module. This is one of the standard utility modules. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iferror Function in Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/iferror-function-in-excel-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/iferror-function-in-excel-example/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T15:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use the IFERROR function to catch errors in Excel. Using the function's parameters, you can return a custom value when specific errors occur.  In this article, you'll learn how to use the IFERROR function to evaluate and handle errors in Excel. You can use the IFERROR function]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Algorithm Closes Quantum Supremacy Window]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=121982</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/new-algorithm-closes-quantum-supremacy-window-20230109/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T14:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Random circuit sampling, a popular technique for showing the power of quantum computers, doesn’t scale up if errors go unchecked.             
The post New Algorithm Closes Quantum Supremacy Window first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Brubaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend Reading — 🧄 Garlic expressions]]></title>
        <id>63b344b0c2cc9537c970afee</id>
        <link href="https://labnotes.org/weekend-reading-garlic-expressions/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-08T23:36:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we draw with SVG, learn garlic expressions, watch an epic battle unfold, explore AI as assistive technology, replace .env with 1P, and bake an octopie.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Assaf Arkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Post Request – How to Send an HTTP Post Request in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-post-request-how-to-send-an-http-post-request-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-post-request-how-to-send-an-http-post-request-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T23:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP requests allow your front-end application to interact successfully with a back-end server or database. One of the five popular HTTP methods for making requests and interacting with your servers is the POST method, which you can use to send data to a server. In this article, you will learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Ternary Operator – Syntax and Example Use Case]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-ternary-operator-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-ternary-operator-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T23:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many operators in JavaScript, one of which is the ternary operator. In this article, I'll explain what this operator is, and how it can be useful when building applications. I have a video version of this topic [https://youtu.be/MmwtZ0AwN9A] you can check out as well to supplement your learning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS by Building the Microsoft Logo 2 Different Ways in Pure CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-microsoft-logo-version-1/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-microsoft-logo-version-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T23:22:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best ways to learn CSS is by creating something useful while you learn. In this article I will show you two ways that you can create the Microsoft logo.  What We Will Be Creating We will create the Microsoft logo in pure CSS. It will look]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dictionary Iteration in Python – How to Iterate Over a Dict with a For Loop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dictionary-iteration-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dictionary-iteration-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T23:16:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, a dictionary is one of the built-in data structures (the others are tuples, lists, and sets). A dictionary is a collection of key:value pairs and you can use them to solve various programming problems. Dictionaries are very flexible to work with. You can get the keys and values]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Logging Works in Laravel Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/laravel-logging/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/laravel-logging/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T19:38:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Logs are records of the events happening with your application. Laravel, by default, writes log information into the laravel.log file that ships with a fresh Laravel installation. The file is housed within the storage > logs  directory.  In this tutorial, you'll learn the following:  * Introduction to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sule-Balogun Olanrewaju Ganiu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Hooks You Can Use in Every Project – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-hooks-every-project-should-use/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-hooks-every-project-should-use/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T19:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hooks are one of the most powerful features of React.  They enable us to easily reuse functionality across our application's components. What's best about hooks is their reusability – you can reuse your hooks both across components and your projects. Here are seven of the most important React hooks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS by Building the YouTube Logo in Pure CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-youtube-logo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-youtube-logo/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T18:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best ways to learn CSS is by creating something useful while you learn. I will show you how to use the following CSS concepts by creating the YouTube logo:  * Flexbox  * The border-radius property  * How to create a triangle in CSS What]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Solidity Modifiers? Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-solidity-modifiers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-solidity-modifiers/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T18:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will explore the various ways you can use modifiers in Solidity to modify the behavior of functions.  We will cover topics such as the syntax for defining and using modifiers, the _;  symbol, using multiple modifiers on a single function, modifiers with arguments, enum-based]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chigozie Oduah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Beginner's Guide to Digital Security – How to Keep Yourself Safe Online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-digital-security/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-digital-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T18:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whatever your connection to technology, security should play a prominent role in the way you think and act.  Technology, after all, amplifies the impact of everything we do with it. The things we say and write using communication technologies can be read and heard by many, many more people]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn to Code & Get a Developer Job in 2023 [Full Book]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-code-book/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-code-book/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T00:52:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to learn to code and get a job as a developer, you're in the right place. This book will show you how. And yes this is the full book – for free – right here on this webpage. A few years back, one of the Big 5]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Go concurrency for 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://golangweekly.com/issues/442</id>
        <link href="https://golangweekly.com/issues/442"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#​442 — January 6, 2023


Unsub  |  Web Version



The Go Weekly Newsletter




  





  
  
Conc: Better Structured Concurrency for Go — Go’s concurrency story is a good one, but Conc aims to make it even safer and easier by providing abstractions for various concepts (think pools, concurrent mapping and iteration, and panic catching) and techniques so that goroutine leaks and unhandled panics can become a thing of the past.
Sourcegraph 


  
  
Go 1.20 Cryptography — The second release candidate of 1.20 is out, and some key crypto changes land, with new implementations of some old (and vulnerable) packages, including a new ECDH package, a replacement for math/big (with a performance hit) with more to come (hopefully…)
Filippo Valsorda 


  
  
Build Your Team’s Private Network with Tail…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Golang Weekly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a File in Linux from the Command Line – Create a File in the Terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-a-file-in-linux-from-the-command-line-create-a-file-in-terminal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-a-file-in-linux-from-the-command-line-create-a-file-in-terminal/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T18:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing files from the command line is one of the most common tasks for a Linux user.  Files are created, edited, deleted, and used by many of the background OS processes. Files are also used by regular users to accomplish daily tasks such as taking notes, writing code, or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Great HTML Form Controls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/perfect-html-input/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/perfect-html-input/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T17:43:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I'm going to show you all the things to consider when building the perfect HTML input. Despite its seemingly simple nature, there's actually a lot that goes into it. How to Make the Control  Well, we need to start somewhere. Might as well start with the control itself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Austin Gil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Check if a File Exists in Python with isFile() and exists()]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-check-if-a-file-exists-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-check-if-a-file-exists-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T17:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with files in Python, there may be times when you need to check whether a file exists or not. But why should you check if a file exists in the first place? Confirming the existence of a specific file comes in handy when you want to perform particular]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Physics Principle That Inspired Modern AI Art]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=121920</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/the-physics-principle-that-inspired-modern-ai-art-20230105/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T17:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diffusion models generate incredible images by learning to reverse the process that, among other things, causes ink to spread through water.            
The post The Physics Principle That Inspired Modern AI Art first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anil Ananthaswamy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Int to String in Java – How to Convert an Integer into a String]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-integer-to-string-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-integer-to-string-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T15:57:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can convert variables from one data type to another in Java using different methods.  In this article, you'll learn how to convert integers to strings in Java in the following ways:  * Using the Integer.toString() method.   * Using the String.valueOf() method.   * Using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Set VS List – Sets and Lists in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-set-vs-list/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-set-vs-list/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T15:52:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, set and list are both data structures for storing and organizing any values. Those values could be numbers, strings, and booleans. In this article, we'll look at the differences between set and list. But before that, let's take a look at what both set and list are. What]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Produce Music with FL Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-produce-music-with-fl-studio/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-produce-music-with-fl-studio/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T15:44:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FL Studio is a powerful digital audio workstation (DAW) used by music producers all over the world. It has a wide range of features that allow users to create, produce, and mix music with ease. Whether you are a beginner or an experienced producer, this course is designed to help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Infinite Scroll in Next.js with Intersection Observer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-infinite-scroll-in-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-infinite-scroll-in-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T15:38:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creators and developers continually come up with new ways to enhance apps and provide value to users.  One feature that's useful for social media and ecommerce apps in particular is infinite scroll. It provides a seamless and intuitive browsing experience by reducing the time it takes to see new]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Divine Orji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Python for Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-python-for-web-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-python-for-web-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T15:33:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python is a popular programming language that is widely used in the development of web applications. It is easy to learn, has a large and active community, and is supported by a wealth of libraries and frameworks. We just published a crash course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Clear Formatting in Excel – Remove Format From a Cell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-clear-formatting-in-excel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-clear-formatting-in-excel/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T01:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I will show you how to clear formatting from a cell in Excel. If you want the quick and dirty version, it's first up and will require you to simply click a couple times.  If you want to become a spreadsheet speedrunner, read this whole, brief]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 React Projects to Build in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-projects-to-improve-your-skills/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-projects-to-improve-your-skills/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T00:22:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to be good at React, building projects is one of the best ways to do it.  I have put together eight different projects that will not only show you what's possible to make with React, but give you some inspiration on what apps to make.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[860+ Free Online Programming & Computer Science Courses You Can Start This New Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-online-programming-cs-courses/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-online-programming-cs-courses/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twelve years ago, universities like Stanford and MIT opened up free online courses [https://www.classcentral.com/] to the public. Today, over 1,200 schools [https://www.classcentral.com/universities] around the world have created thousands of free online courses. To welcome the new year, I’ve compiled this list of 860+ such free online courses that you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhawal Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Format Compact Numbers with the JavaScript Internationalization API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/format-compact-numbers-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/format-compact-numbers-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T15:39:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes it can be difficult to fit large numbers into your site or app's layout, especially if you have to display several of them together.  As a result, a lot of modern sites and apps use the same format to display large numbers in a compact way. For example,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gerard Hynes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Ancient Asteroids, Gamma Rays Made Building Blocks of Life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=121879</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/inside-ancient-asteroids-gamma-rays-made-building-blocks-of-life-20230104/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T15:28:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new radiation-based mechanism adds to the ways that amino acids could have been made in space and brought to the young Earth.            
The post Inside Ancient Asteroids, Gamma Rays Made Building Blocks of Life first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Rennie and Allison Parshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Custom Ghost CMS Theme]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-ghost-cms-theme/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-ghost-cms-theme/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T15:20:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ghost CMS is a platform specifically designed for bloggers and writers. Using Ghost, you can quickly get a blog website up and running.  Ghost targets primarily writers and all the features are specifically built for writing.  Ghost's new dashboard gives you a user-friendly interface, and beginners can easily]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Call Graph? And How to Generate them Automatically]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-automate-call-graph-creation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-automate-call-graph-creation/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T23:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever found yourself staring at lines of code, trying to wrap your head around how all the different functions fit together and interact with each other?  It can be a daunting task, especially in larger, more complex programs.  But fear not! There is a way to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel García Solla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Higher Order Functions in JavaScript – Explained with Practical Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/higher-order-functions-in-javascript-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/higher-order-functions-in-javascript-explained/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T22:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a web developer, you should always strive to learn new techniques and discover ways to work smarter with JavaScript.  One such technique is using higher order functions. Higher order functions are functions that take one or more functions as arguments, or return a function as their result. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sobit Prasad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Format Dates with Ordinal Number Suffixes (-st, -nd, -rd, -th) in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/format-dates-with-ordinal-number-suffixes-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/format-dates-with-ordinal-number-suffixes-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T21:57:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many online resources teach you how to format dates. But it's hard to find any that explain how to format dates with an ordinal number suffix (like 1st) in JavaScript – without using a library. In this short article, you will learn how to format dates in JavaScript with ordinal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python join() – How to Combine a List into a String in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-join-how-to-combine-a-list-into-a-string-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-join-how-to-combine-a-list-into-a-string-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T20:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[join() is one of the built-in string functions in Python that lets us create a new string from a list of string elements with a user-defined separator.  Today we'll explore join() and learn about:  * join() syntax  * how to use join() to combine a list into]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suchandra Datta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a React App With a .NET Core Backend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-react-app-with-a-dot-net-backend/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-react-app-with-a-dot-net-backend/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T19:57:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ASP.NET Core can work well as a backend for your React apps. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to to create a basic React application that leverages a .NET Web API Component written in C#. In order to integrate React with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is XSS? How to Protect Your Website from DOM Cross-Site Scripting Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-protect-against-dom-xss-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-protect-against-dom-xss-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T19:51:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Website security issues and vulnerabilities are a global problem as cyber security vulnerabilities are increasing. We have seen a major rise in the average number of these cases in the past few years, and 2021 saw an all-time high. So in this tutorial, we are going to talk about DOM]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrej Kovacevic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Basic User Authentication in a Flask App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-setup-user-authentication-in-flask/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-setup-user-authentication-in-flask/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T14:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[User authentication is important for protecting sensitive information and resources from unauthorized access. It helps ensure that only authorized users can access and make changes to data, and helps prevent unauthorized users from gaining access to sensitive information. There are different methods for implementing user authentication, including password-based authentication, token-based]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Researcher, Long Out of Math, Cracks Devilish Problem About Sets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=121812</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/long-out-of-math-an-ai-programmer-cracks-a-pure-math-problem-20230103/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T14:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On nights and weekends, Justin Gilmer attacked an old question in pure math using the tools of information theory.            
The post Google Researcher, Long Out of Math, Cracks Devilish Problem About Sets first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Hartnett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laravel Valet Performance – How to Prevent 504 Errors and Speed Up Valet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/speed-up-performance-in-laravel-valet/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/speed-up-performance-in-laravel-valet/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-02T23:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, I decided to install Laravel Valet on my Mac. But after the installation, the performance of the microservice architecture application I had it on was quite slow.  I wondered if it was an M1 issue or because I had yet to shut the machine down. I shut]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sule-Balogun Olanrewaju Ganiu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn React in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-learn-react-in-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-learn-react-in-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-02T22:59:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the most popular JavaScript library for building frontend applications, there has never been a better year to learn React than 2023.  In this guide, I'm going to show you the most valuable resources and tips that I believe will help you learn React faster. You'll also save a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS by Building the Figma Logo in Pure CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-by-creating-the-figma-logo-in-pure-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-by-creating-the-figma-logo-in-pure-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-02T22:39:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best ways to learn CSS is by creating something useful while you learn. I will show you how to use the following CSS concepts by creating the Figma logo:  * flex-wrap  * multiple classes  * border-radius What We Will Be Creating We will create]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Your Privacy Online – Five Useful Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-protect-your-privacy-online/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-protect-your-privacy-online/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-02T22:33:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s growing cyber threat landscape, it is important to learn how to protect yourself. In this article, I'll share my five favorite tools you can use to protect your privacy online. Why Online Privacy is Important Have you ever wondered how valuable your data is? Every app, website, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add a Custom Network to Metamask with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-custom-network-to-metamask/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-custom-network-to-metamask/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-02T22:17:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a developer, you can enhance the user experience of your decentralized applications (DApps) by allowing users to easily add your network to their Metamask wallet with just one click.  This simplifies the process of onboarding users to your application, since they don't have to manually add the network]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Omobola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[File Permissions in Linux – How to Use the chmod Command]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/file-permissions-in-linux-chmod-command-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/file-permissions-in-linux-chmod-command-explained/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-02T22:17:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just as with other operating systems, multiple users can create user accounts and share the same machine running Linux OS.  But whenever different users share a system, problems of privacy can easily arise. The first user may not wish the next user to view, edit, or delete their files,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend Reading — 👋 Happy new year!]]></title>
        <id>63b1d35fc2cc9537c970a3cd</id>
        <link href="https://labnotes.org/weekend-reading-happy-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-02T20:52:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m ready for 2023, are you? This week we got fresh UI components, rendering HTML with React, GPT prompt reverse engineering, and ultimate LEGO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Assaf Arkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to disable Google sign-in prompts on other sites (#tilPost)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/today-i-learned/how-to-disable-google-sign-in-prompts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/today-i-learned/how-to-disable-google-sign-in-prompts/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-28T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suppose you're using Google Services like Gmail; you can log into other services with Google Sign-In. That's great if you're logged in all the time and don't mind Google watching every one of your moves.
If you're using Gmail and Chrome, privacy's a lost cause anyways, but let's not get into this topic.
Now, even though I use Gmail, I prefer to sign in with Email/Password combinations and let my password manager do its magic. And with this setup, I don't need yet another modal begging for attention. 👇
Thanks to Ricky Mondello, today I learned you can disable Google's Sign-In nudges in your account settings!
Thank goodness — less pop-ups are more fun!


          
          
            Reply to Stefan]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend Reading — 👋 2-3 levels max]]></title>
        <id>63a8b308387fff68fb190974</id>
        <link href="https://labnotes.org/weekend-reading-2-3-levels-max/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-26T21:38:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our train leaves every 5 minutes, we capture some packets, zoom through meetings, and buy bubble wrap in bulk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Assaf Arkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn to Code RPG Version 1.5 is Now Playable with Hours of New Gameplay]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-code-rpg-1-5-update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-code-rpg-1-5-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T02:43:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello from the Learn to Code RPG dev team! We are Lynn, KayLa, and Nielda. And we've been hard at work building out new adventures for our characters. I'm excited to announce the launch of Learn to Code RPG v1.5, a year after the launch of Learn to Code RPG]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lynn Zheng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Cache Expensive Database Queries Using the Momento Serverless Cache]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serverless-caching-for-your-web-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serverless-caching-for-your-web-applications/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T20:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When to Use a Cache When you are building a web-application, you'll need to fetch data from a database. As your traffic and the size of your database grows, you will find that querying your database gets slower and slower. In order to return requests to users quickly, a cache]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Brown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[String Equality in JavaScript – How to Compare Strings in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/string-equality-in-javascript-how-to-compare-strings-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/string-equality-in-javascript-how-to-compare-strings-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T18:57:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When writing code or building a solution, you might need to compare two strings to see if they are the same before proceeding with an operation. For example, when a user signs in, you'll want to compare the username the provide to the one in your database to see if]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding to a Dict in Python – How to Add to a Dictionary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/adding-to-a-dict-in-python-how-to-add-to-a-dictionary/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/adding-to-a-dict-in-python-how-to-add-to-a-dictionary/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T18:04:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Python dictionary is like a JavaScript object – it’s a sequence of key:value  pairs. So, you can create them like this: stack_dict = {     "frontend": "JavaScript",     "backend": "Node JS",     "markup": "HTML and JSX", } To access]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Execution Context – How JS Works Behind the Scenes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-javascript-works-behind-the-scene-javascript-execution-context/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-javascript-works-behind-the-scene-javascript-execution-context/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T17:50:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how JavaScript works behind the scenes? It's actually quite fascinating! And that's what you'll learn about here. JavaScript is a single-threaded interpreted language. Every browser has its own JavaScript engine. Google Chrome has the V8 engine, Mozilla Firefox has SpiderMonkey, and so on. They all are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rwitesh Bera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Year in Comments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=121394</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/thoughtful-and-funny-feedback-from-quantas-audience-in-2022-20221222/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T17:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the internet is awash in the noise of unmoderated comments, Quanta has attempted to provide a quiet, information-rich spot where readers, listeners and viewers can contemplate the complexity of nature.              
The post The Year in Comments first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Carlstrom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Year in Math]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=121400</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/the-biggest-math-breakthroughs-in-2022-20221222/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T16:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four Fields Medals were awarded for major breakthroughs in geometry, combinatorics, statistical physics and number theory, even as mathematicians continued to wrestle with how computers are changing the discipline.            
The post The Year in Math first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Konstantin Kakaes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is enumerate() in Python? Enumeration Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-enumerate-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-enumerate-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T15:56:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The enumerate() function is one of the built-in functions in Python. It provides a handy way to access each item in an iterable, along with a count value that specifies the order in which the item was accessed.  In this article you will learn all that you need to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suchandra Datta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Year in Physics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=121396</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/the-biggest-discoveries-in-physics-in-2022-20221222/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T15:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a year filled with sweet new observations in astronomy and tantalizing breakthroughs in condensed matter physics, the brand-new space telescope takes the cake.            
The post The Year in Physics first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie Wolchover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Viewport units can consider the writing mode (#tilPost)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/today-i-learned/viewport-units-can-consider-the-writing-mode/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/today-i-learned/viewport-units-can-consider-the-writing-mode/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slowly but surely, developers adopt logical CSS properties to be good web citizens and write CSS that follows a defined writing mode, directionality, and text orientation.
width becomes inline-size, margin-inline is a shorthand for margin-left and margin-right, you get the idea.
MDN lists all the logical CSS properties if you haven't heard about them yet.
That's all good and dandy, but there's at least one situation where logical CSS properties aren't enough. Suppose you want to style a container and make it 50% of the viewport on the horizontal axis.
You can define inline-size: 50vw; but isn't that mixing things up? inline-size will define either the horizontal or vertical size depending on the writing mode, but 50vw will always be the viewport width.
I don't know if that's a real issue b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to animate an element's height with CSS grid (#snippet)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/snippets/how-to-animate-height-with-css-grid/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/snippets/how-to-animate-height-with-css-grid/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did Chris just publish a post and unveil the solution to a long-lasting CSS problem almost in a side sentence? It seems like it!
What of the many are we walking about? We're talking about animating an element's height from 0 to something (auto).
Animated grid rows

Not too long ago, browsers shipped animatable CSS grid columns and rows which you could use to fly in a side menu or do fancy stuff like Michelle Barker. 👇
 by Michelle Barker (@michellebarker)
  on CodePen.

I've never considered using animated grid rows to hide grid cells, though.
Here's the trick to toggle an element's height:
define a grid element
define a single grid row with 0fr
add a transition for grid-template-rows
set overflow: hidden to the one element inside the grid
redefine the grid-template-rows to be 1fr with an open class
.grid {
  display: grid;
  grid-template-rows: 0fr;
  transition: grid-template-rows 0.5s ease-in-out;
}

.grid.open {
  grid-template-rows: 1fr;
}

.grid-inner {
  overflow: hidden;
}

And voila! You can now transition an element's height, and it doesn't use any hardcoded values – toggle a class and call it a day! CSS Grid figures out all the rest.
[Interactive component: visit the article to see it...]
I'm blown away by this!
And sure, to Chris' point, it'd be nice to have an easier way to animate element heights, but I'll take this approach for now! Thanks Chris! 💯


          
          
            Reply to Stefan]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Filtering in C# – How to Filter a List with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/filtering-in-csharp-how-to-filter-a-list-with-code-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/filtering-in-csharp-how-to-filter-a-list-with-code-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T21:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Filtering through a data set is one of the most basic operations a developer should know how to perform.  Filtering [https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/csharp/programming-guide/concepts/linq/filtering-data]  refers to the process of restricting the result set to contain only those elements that satisfy a specified condition. It is also known as selection.  To]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeError: can't multiply sequence by non-int of type float [Solved Python Error]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typeerror-cant-multiply-sequence-by-non-int-of-type-float-solved-python-error-3/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typeerror-cant-multiply-sequence-by-non-int-of-type-float-solved-python-error-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T21:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most times when you encounter errors while coding, you can discover the reason why the error is occurring and how you can fix it in the error message. The Python error, "TypeError: can't multiply sequence by non-int of type float" is no exception to that. I have prepared this article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Scapy – Python Networking Tool Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-scapy-python-networking/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-scapy-python-networking/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T21:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post you will learn about an amazing tool named Scapy. Scapy is a Python library that enables us to send, sniff, and dissect network frames.  It is useful in a variety of use cases, one of which is to actually get some hands-on experience when you learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Concurrent Programming in Go – Goroutines, Channels, and More Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/concurrent-programming-in-go/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/concurrent-programming-in-go/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T19:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concurrency refers to a programming language's ability to deal with lots of things at once. A good way to understand concurrency is by imagining multiple cars traveling on two lanes. Sometimes the cars overtake each other, and sometimes they stop and let others pass by. Another good example is when]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rwitesh Bera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Download and Trim MP3s from YouTube with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/download-trim-mp3-from-youtube-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/download-trim-mp3-from-youtube-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T18:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everybody's different, but I believe that nearly all of us enjoy listening to music. If you want to keep a local version of audio streams you often listen to, you'll need to download these files. Sometimes you'll also want to clip a portion of this audio file instead of having]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Otavio Ehrenberger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Abstraction in Programming? Explained for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-abstraction-in-programming-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-abstraction-in-programming-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T18:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article will not be a dry and boring explanation of abstract classes, interfaces, protocols, or similar software entities. I will explain what they are in simple terms, but my main goal is to change how you think about abstractions in general. All of this is in service of helping]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Michael Kay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Santa Tracker App with Next.js and React Leaflet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-santa-tracker-app-with-next-js-react-leaflet/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-santa-tracker-app-with-next-js-react-leaflet/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T16:42:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's the holiday season and Santa's coming! But just like he watches all of us, we can build a map-based tracking app to keep an eye on him and find out when he'll come on Christmas night with Next.js and React Leaflet.  *  How can we track Santa?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colby Fayock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Database Normalization – Normal Forms 1nf 2nf 3nf Table Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/database-normalization-1nf-2nf-3nf-table-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/database-normalization-1nf-2nf-3nf-table-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T16:40:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In relational databases, especially large ones, you need to arrange entries so that other maintainers and administrators can read them and work on them. This is why database normalization is important. In simple words, database normalization entails organizing a database into several tables in order to reduce redundancy. You can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Stunning QR Codes with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-stunning-qr-codes-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-stunning-qr-codes-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T15:40:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A quick response (QR) code is a barcode that a digital device can easily scan. It encodes data as a series of pixels in a square grid.  Tracking information about supply chains using QR codes is very useful in marketing and advertising campaigns. The International Organization for Standardization certified]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Year in Computer Science]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=121398</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/the-biggest-discoveries-in-computer-science-in-2022-20221221/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T14:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computer scientists this year learned how to transmit perfect secrets, why transformers seem so good at everything, and how to improve on decades-old algorithms (with a little help from AI).            
The post The Year in Computer Science first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Andrews</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Year in Biology]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=121402</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/major-biology-discoveries-from-2022-20221221/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T14:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Momentum for new ideas in Alzheimer’s research joined advances in neuroscience, developmental biology and origin-of-life studies to make 2022 a memorable year of biological insights.            
The post The Year in Biology first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Rennie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Fullertubes’ Join the Family of Carbon Crystals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=121664</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/fullertubes-join-the-family-of-carbon-crystals-20221220/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T15:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The buckminsterfullerene revolution never came, but some researchers are eagerly exploring the properties of newfound carbon crystals known as fullertubes.            
The post ‘Fullertubes’ Join the Family of Carbon Crystals first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James R. Riordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your Own SaaS – PagerDuty Clone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-your-own-saas-pagerduty-clone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-your-own-saas-pagerduty-clone/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T13:47:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best ways to learn software development is to create a slimmed-down version of software you use every day to get a better understanding of how it might work. This process helps you understand the problem space constraints and techniques required to build a real-world use-case. We just]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Your First Job in InfoSec]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-your-first-job-in-infosec/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-your-first-job-in-infosec/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T23:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting your first job in information security (infosec, or cybersecurity) can be tough.  It's (still) a relatively new industry, and job roles and descriptions aren't always consistent. Plus, it can be hard to figure out where to get started, what skills you need, and how you can acquire them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Kaczanowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend Reading — 👋 Friend of John]]></title>
        <id>6396477892a0bb4700d50e0c</id>
        <link href="https://labnotes.org/weekend-reading-friend-of-john/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T21:58:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we discover the legendary software entrepreneur J.Mastodon, punch holes in cards, choose a new timezone, and worry about dark chocolate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Assaf Arkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Have Fun Building React Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/have-fun-building-react-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/have-fun-building-react-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T21:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building React apps can either be a very fun experience or a very difficult and tedious one, based off of the tools you choose. React is a JavaScript library that, unlike frameworks like Angular, leave us to making a lot of decisions on our own. You have to choose which]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your Own Wireguard VPN in Five Minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-your-own-wireguard-vpn-in-five-minutes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-your-own-wireguard-vpn-in-five-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T20:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may already understand how important a good VPN can be for maintaining the security and privacy of your mobile communications.  Whether you need to use your phone for banking over a public airport or coffee shop WiFi connection, or you're worried about the wrong people listening in on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Speed up Your Software Development Pipeline]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-speed-up-your-software-development-pipeline/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-speed-up-your-software-development-pipeline/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T17:51:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever managed a software development pipeline—or have plans to do so—there's one thing you'll need to prioritize above almost all else: speed.  No matter the type of software you're working on, you'll always be under pressure to speed up your team's deliverables. Some of that pressure might]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrej Kovacevic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[She Finds Keys to Ecology in Cells That Steal From Others]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=121543</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/holly-moeller-finds-keys-to-ecology-in-cells-that-steal-20221219/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T14:53:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ecologist Holly Moeller studies microorganisms that expand their range by absorbing organelles and gaining new metabolic talents from their prey.            
The post She Finds Keys to Ecology in Cells That Steal From Others first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veronique Greenwood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Weekly #89 (#blogPost)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/web-weekly-89/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/web-weekly-89/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-18T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frohe Feiertage!

Would you animate the display property if you could? Have you heard of the new renderblockingstatus webperf property? Or did you already inject DOM elements with before() and after()?
All the answers and much more are included in this week's Web Weekly. 🫣
Before we go into this week's favorites...
Last week I asked for a reply to this email to signal email providers that I'm not spamming and well... I DOS'ed myself. Way more of you replied to the email, and it was a good challenge to reply to all the emails. 🫣
Sending this newsletter sometimes feels a little lonely, but I'm humbled that so many people are reading along! And I can't tell you how much getting all these kind words and replies motivate me.
I'm all ears when you have something to share or want to provide fee…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Raycast snippet auto expansion (#blogPost)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/how-to-use-raycast-snippet-auto-expansion/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/how-to-use-raycast-snippet-auto-expansion/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-18T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I plugged that I use Raycast for automatic snippet expansion in my weekly newsletter. If you don't know Raycast, it's a macOS Spotlight replacement and the OS-level command bar is very good!
I use Raycast primarily to navigate all the apps on my machine, place windows on different monitors and expand snippets. ;es for example, expands automatically to my email address. Whether in my browser, mail app or Slack, my email address or often used phrases are automagically expanded to save some keystrokes.
But I must admit, the docs on auto-expansion could be better, and someone asked me how I set this functionality up. So here we go!
The native snippet extension

Raycast comes with a native snippet extension to create and search all your snippets from within Raycast itself.
I'm not using it to search my snippets, because I primarily auto-expand things. And to enable auto-expansion, you must look at the overall snippet configuration.
"Enable Snippet Expansion" is the magic trick. After you enable this setting, use the "Create Snippet" or "Edit snippet" command via the Raycast command bar and define a name, the expansion and the character combination triggering it (Keyword).
And that's it!


          
          
            Reply to Stefan]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>