<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://daorren.github.io/osmofeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-01-21T01:20:28.192Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://daorren.github.io/osmofeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://daorren.github.io/osmofeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend Reading — Where's my car?]]></title>
        <id>65a2e15859af5c0502c7562c</id>
        <link href="https://labnotes.org/weekend-reading-wheres-my-car/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T18:26:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we find the missing car, test with cats, remember old computing machines, follow the layoffs on TikTok, ask the chicken the question, and build our Mac with Lego bricks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Assaf Arkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible notifications (#note)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/notes/accessible-notifications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/notes/accessible-notifications/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sara Soueidan just published a free chapter of her Practical Accessibility course; with no surprise, it's high quality.
The chapter is split into two blog posts:
Accessible notifications with ARIA Live Regions (Part 1)
Accessible notifications with ARIA Live Regions (Part 2)
I strongly suggest you read these, but disclaimer: you'll need a while to make yourself through them.
For my archive, here are some rough notes from reading the chapter.
Live region roles vs. the aria-live attribute

To define an element as a live region, you can use the aria-live attribute or go with a live region role (alert, status, log, marquee or timer). From all these roles, alert and status are fair game because they're well supported.
Regions have one advantage over the aria-live attribute.
Another advantage to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to exclude elements from being shown in Google Search results (#tilPost)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/today-i-learned/how-to-exclude-elements-from-being-shown-in-google-search-results/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/today-i-learned/how-to-exclude-elements-from-being-shown-in-google-search-results/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's look at what happens when I google myself.
Of course, I know how my site is structured, and I can tell that Google displays my site's title and the description includes some of the root page's headlines. The description is not the worst, but it certainly could be better.
Is there a way to exclude elements from being shown in the Google snippet?
Today I learned that there is! And the solution is based on an HTML data attribute: data-nosnippet. Here's the example snippet from the Google Search Central docs:
<p>This text can be shown in a snippet
<span data-nosnippet>and this part would not be shown</span>.</p>

<div data-nosnippet>not in snippet</div>
<div data-nosnippet="true">also not in snippet</div>
<div data-nosnippet="false">also not in snippet</div>

data-nosnippet works on div, span and section elements, and it doesn't care what value you'll give it. data-nosnippet="true" and data-nosnippet="false" have the same result — signaling that this element shouldn't pop up in the Google Search results. Nice!
If you're unhappy with the search results, add some juicy data attributes now. But remember to trigger a reindex in the Search Console. Otherwise, it might take a while until your changes have an effect.


          
          
            Reply to Stefan]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to do math in shell environments (bash, zsh, ...) (#tilPost)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/today-i-learned/math-in-shell-environments/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/today-i-learned/math-in-shell-environments/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was kneedeep into CI/CD scripting, when I hit a wall. You can't just do simple math like adding or subtracting integers in a shell environment? How could I have not discovered this fact before?
As it turns out, simple operations like summing and subtracting two variables need some serious shell knowledge.
Here's the problem.
#!/bin/sh

a=1
b=2
c=$a+$b
echo $c # 1+2

When evaluating c, $a and $b are resolved to their values (1 and 2), but the + is treated as a string. All three parts are strings, and now the result is 1+2. Ufff.
After researching this problem, I learned that there are multiple ways to do math in shell environments. Let's find out what I learned!
The expr command

Let's start with my first Google result — expr.
#!/bin/sh

a=1
b=2
c=`expr $a + $b`

echo $c #3

Backticks and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Weekly #119 (#blogPost)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/web-weekly-119/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/web-weekly-119/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings! 👋

Does sticky content harm accessibility? Is it time for a native toggle button on the web? And what makes a good touch target?
This week's Web Weekly includes all the answers and much more!
But before we start, if you've subscribed to Web Weekly for a while, you might have noticed that I dropped the music picks. And I miss them.
So here's an idea: I'd love to include you and add a section that looks like this:
[YOUR NAME] listens to "[BAND] — [Title]" and says:

"I just love how bouncy this track is!"

Are you game? If so, let me know!
Last week, I shared "Dark Visitors" — a site listing known AI agents.  And there are a lot! Knowing about them is good, but what should we do with this info? Do we really need to ship a robots.txt with hundreds of agent definitions to tell them…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend Reading — Layoffs, explained]]></title>
        <id>6599841af9520504e51ba198</id>
        <link href="https://labnotes.org/weekend-reading-layoffs-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T19:13:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we have a collection of interesting software, Windows 95 for React, a brief explanation of layoffs, a beautiful AI device, a caffeinated Jupiter, and a mouse to clean our house.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Assaf Arkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Weekly #118 (#blogPost)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/web-weekly-118/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/web-weekly-118/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Guten Tag! Guten Tag! 👋

How can you block AI agents from using your content? Is centering elements in CSS really a problem in 2024? What's in for browser interop 2024?
This week's Web Weekly includes all the answers and much more. Enjoy!
I'm no designer. And unfortunately, I rarely have a visual sense to create really beautiful things.
But I did learn some simple rules and tricks that move my designs from the "You designed this yourself, or?" stage to "Yeah, looks okay.".
Give elements space to breathe.
Don't put pure black on pure white.
Distribute things evenly.
Don't break the visual grid!
You get the idea. And I'm really just applying the rules I know.
And I just learned some more rules! Anthony Hobday collected a whole lot of safe design practices. They're easy to follow and put int…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend Reading — Happy and safe new year!]]></title>
        <id>6590533ff9520504e51b9526</id>
        <link href="https://labnotes.org/weekend-reading-happy-and-safe-new-year/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T16:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we run a desktop in the browser, re-learn JavaScript and React Server Components, cover a bunch of cool developer tools, revisit inclusive design, write a brag document, get ourselves a free VPN, and snack on a Shoeshi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Assaf Arkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend Reading — Hot Potatoes]]></title>
        <id>65872981f9520504e51b8aaf</id>
        <link href="https://labnotes.org/weekend-reading-hot-potatoes/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T17:27:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we decide on monolithic vs micro-service, Remix all the things, run a performance comparison, get better at making decisions, say farewell to Firefox and Substack, exercise every morning, recommend two things you can watch online, and collect our New Year’s event tickets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Assaf Arkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone Selling an MEV bot is a Scammer]]></title>
        <id>https://mteam88.github.io/posts/anyone-selling-an-mev-bot-is-a-scammer/</id>
        <link href="https://mteam88.github.io/posts/anyone-selling-an-mev-bot-is-a-scammer/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-24T03:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don't fall for scams. MEV bots are not for sale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mteam's Writings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend Reading — Trick AI bot into selling Tahoe for $1]]></title>
        <id>657de1ac43f4111d84b5f497</id>
        <link href="https://labnotes.org/weekend-reading-trick-ai-bot-into-selling-tahoe-for-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T18:38:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we discuss whether HTML is necessary, get a new calendaring app, cover some productivity hacks, balk at AI Gone Wrong, and advise you how to wrap your x-max presents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Assaf Arkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local link targets must be focusable to prevent accessibility issues (#tilPost)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stefanjudis.com/today-i-learned/relative-html-links-focus-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/today-i-learned/relative-html-links-focus-issues/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might think that when you bet on the web platform and rely on native HTML features, your website will be completely accessible. Unfortunately, this assumption is wrong in many cases.
If you want to learn about more inaccessible HTML features, a recent HTMHell article covered many of them. It's a great read!
This week, I've learned that even simple things, such as linking to local elements via id (<a href="#something">), require careful consideration not to cause accessibility problems.
What's the issue with local links?
document.activeElement is only set to focusable elements

I've been reading How To Avoid Breaking Web Pages For Keyboard Users and learned that some assistive technologies rely on document.activeElement.
The activeElement read-only property of the Document interface ret…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis Web Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>